嘿,西奥。这里太黑了。
Hey, Theo. It's so dark in here.
-你在施魔法吗?——没有。
- You doin' some magic? - No.
是啊，我有一段时间没看过你表演魔术了。
Yeah, I haven't seen you do any tricks in a while.
好吧，我想我会忘记寄给你的邮件。
Well, guess I'll forget about what came in the mail for you.
我的邮件里有什么?
What came in the mail for me?
你被邀请来参加这个地方…魔法学院。
You've been invited to attend this place... The Institute of Magic.
它在山上。这是一个为期五周的强化学习。
It's up in the mountains. It's a five-week intensive study where...
我知道魔法学院是什么了。
I know what the Institute of Magic is.
爸爸和我经常谈论这件事。
Dad and I used to talk about it all the time.
你内心有个声音，这个声音在说，
There's a voice inside of you, and it's the voice that says,
“我想成为一个魔术师。”
"I want to be a magician."
你好,西奥。
Hello, Theo.
他怎么知道我的名字的?
How did he know my name?
我怎么知道你的名字?你的申请表上有。
How did I know your name? It was on your application.
西奥，我是国家宝藏罗伊·普雷斯顿，我也听到了声音。
Theo, I'm national treasure Roy Preston, and I hear voices too.
三年前，我成立了魔法学院，
Shribbity-three-ish years ago, I founded the Institute of Magic,
为有前途的年轻魔术师而设的音乐学院。
a conservatory for promising young magicians.
在这里，世界著名的魔术师将教你七种魔术。
Here, world-famous magicians will teach you the seven types of magic.
花招。
Sleight of hand.
预测。
Prediction.
恢复。
Restoration.
消失……和外表。
Vanish... and appearance.
固体……通过固体。
Solid... through solid.
逃跑。
Escape.
悬浮。
Levitation.
然后你就可以表演了
And you will get to perform
在世界著名的罗伊·普雷斯顿纪念剧院。
in the world-famous Roy Preston Prememorial Theater.
你会和其他年轻的魔术师建立持久的关系。
And you'll build lasting relationships with other young magicians.
即使是那些奇怪的。因为在这里，我们都是怪胎。
Even the weird ones. Because here, we're all the weird ones.
哇。很酷的鸟,兰德尔。
Wow. Cool bird, Randall.
但不要相信我的话。今年夏天你自己来看看吧。
But don't take my word for it. Come see for yourself this summer.
魔法营听起来很酷吧?
Magic camp sounds pretty cool?
这不是“魔法营”。是魔法学院。
It's not "magic camp." It's the Institute of Magic.
这完全是著名的。
It's totally famous.
但我不知道。
But I don't know.
今年夏天我应该呆在家里。
I should stay home this summer.
你需要我来修剪草坪和招待卡梅隆
You need me to mow the lawn and to entertain Cameron.
我很好。而且你也没那么有趣。
I'm fine. And you're not that entertaining.
我想你可能对这个感兴趣，但如果你不感兴趣，也没关系。
I thought you might be interested in this, but if you're not, that's okay.
等待。
Wait.
爸爸总是说他想让我去那里。
Dad always said he wanted me to go there.
他以前一定申请过我……你知道的。
He must have applied for me before... you know.
如果爸爸肯花时间帮我申请，我也许应该……
If Dad took the time to apply for me, I should probably...
你可以花整个夏天修剪草坪，
You could spend the summer mowing the lawn,
或者你可以和世界上最伟大的魔术师一起学习魔术。
or you can study magic with the world's greatest magicians.
-你有票吗?——亲爱的。
- Do you have the tickets? - Honey.
-不，我没有票。-你拿到票了!
- No, I don't have the tickets. - You have the tickets!
“这一代最伟大的魔术师。”是的,对的。
"This generation's greatest magician." Yeah, right.
我们在里约热内卢电视台看到Penn和Teller。
We're seeing Penn and Teller at the Rio.
太好了。
Great.
-昨晚我们看到了克里斯·达伍德。——头脑吹。
- Last night we saw Kris Darkwood. - Minds blown.
然后黑木让凯撒的大卫雕像完全消失了。
And then Darkwood made the David statue at Caesars totally disappear.
我的头还在爆炸。
My head is still exploding.
克里斯汀娜·达伍德在维加斯有最令人兴奋的表演。
Kristina Darkwood has the most mind-blowing show in Vegas.
这不是令人兴奋的。你的头不会爆炸，我保证。
It's not mind-blowing. Your head will not explode, I promise you.
天啊。这里面有什么?
Geez. What do you got in this thing?
汤!
Soup!
我很抱歉。我发誓我有一张20美元的钞票。
I'm so sorry. I swear I had a 20-dollar bill in here.
它去了哪里?也许在这里。我去找找看。
Where did it go? Maybe it's in here. I'll look for it.
我的。不，不在这里。
My. No, it's not here.
在这儿。
Here it is.
——找到它。!谢天谢地。
- Found it. ! Thank heavens.
我可以要回12美元吗?
Can I have $12 back?
上次我试着做个好人。
Last time I try to be a nice guy.
“好”可能有点言过其实了。
"Nice" may be an overstatement.
罗伊。嘿。你在这里做什么?
Roy. Hey. What are you doing here?
拉斯维加斯,宝贝。
Vegas, baby.
另外，你能送我到希望街123号吗?
Also, can you take me to 123 Hope Street, please?
安迪，生意怎么样?
So, Andy, how's business?
生活的梦想。
Living the dream.
我刚学会了一个叫做“Uber把我的工资减半”的新把戏。
I just learned this awesome new trick called "Uber cuts my paychecks in half."
嗯，你很幸运，因为今年夏天我有一个顾问空缺。
Well, you are in luck because I have a counselor opening this summer.
大卫·布莱恩退出了，你是我想到的第一个名字。
David Blaine dropped out, and you were the first name I thought of.
——真的吗?-是的。
- Really? - Yeah.
大卫·布莱恩退出了，我是名单上的第二个名字。
David Blaine drops out, and I'm the second name on the list.
我从没说过你是名单上的第二名。
I never said you were the second name on the list.
我说你是我想到的第一个人。
I said you were the first person I thought of.
你是…
You were...
你在名单上排名很靠后。
You were pretty far down there on the list.
我很欣赏你的直率诚实，但我不再施魔法了。
Well, I appreciate your blunt honesty, but I don't do magic anymore.
我已经很长时间没有了。用黑木制作自…
I haven't for a long time. Ever since Darkwood...
是的。我很抱歉，我不怪你。
Yes. I'm so sorry and I-I don't blame you.
——真的吗?——没有。
- Really? - No.
你不能全心全意地爱上魔术
You cannot love magic with your whole heart
直到你的心再次完整。
until your heart is whole again.
这就是……与魔法有关的陈词滥调听起来很深奥
And there it is... the magic-related clichés which sound profound
但实际上毫无意义。
but are actually meaningless.
你知道，我会想念那些，但我还是不会回来。
You know, I'm gonna miss those, but I'm still not coming back.
Kris将在今年夏天回归。
Kris is coming back this summer.
用黑木制作- - - - - - ?-克里斯·达伍德，是的。
- Darkwood? - Kris Darkwood, yeah.
所以她会有她自己的小屋我也会有我自己的小屋?
So she would have her own cabin and I would have my own cabin?
你们两个都将与年轻的魔术师紧密合作。
Both of you will be working very closely with the, young magicians.
那大礼帽呢?你现在还这么做，对吧?这是一间小屋对一间小屋，胜者全得?
And the Top Hat? You still do that, right? It's cabin versus cabin, winner takes all?
是的，我的意思是，你知道高帽比赛是怎么运作的。
Yes, I mean, you know how the Top Hat competition works.
哦，Weiners的世界。好了。希望您预订了房间。
Ooh, World Of Weiners. Nice. Hope you got a reservation.
不管怎样，想一想。
Anyway, think about it.
因为我知道你还能让他们走…
Because I know you can still make 'em go...
“哇。”
"Wow."
那家伙很好。
That guy is good.
忘记了我的电话。你能把我的电话递给我吗?
Forgot my phone. Can you hand me my phone?
哦。那将是一个非常酷的退出。
Ooh. That would have been a really cool exit.
你知道我买了多少热狗他们才会让我这么做吗?
You know how many hot dogs I had to buy so they would let me do that to the sign?
一百年。我也不会骄傲地说我吃了14个。
A hundred. And I'm not proud to say I ate 14 of them.
-给你。-玩得开心，保罗。
- Here it is. - Have fun, Paul.
——获得乐趣。女孩,再见。再见!
- Have fun. - Bye-bye girls. Bye!
再见!
Bye!
这些都是世界闻名的魔术师吗?
These are all world-famous magicians?
-他们看起来像一群ner…-要交新朋友。
- They look like a bunch of ner... - New friends to make.
再告诉我一遍。
Tell me one more time.
毒葛有三个杏仁状的小叶，颜色从浅绿色到红色，
Poison ivy has three almond-shaped leaflets, light green to red in color,
常在水源附近发现。
often found near a water source.
经常，但不总是，内森。来吧，把你的脑袋放进去!
Often but not always, Nathan. Come on, get your head in the game!
妈妈，爸爸，我有我的肾上腺素注射器，我的费内根
Mother, Father, I've got my EpiPen, my Phenergan,
我的手镯上用十种语言写着"花生过敏"
my bracelet that says "peanut allergy" in ten languages.
还有我的尿滤器以防我被困在什么地方
Plus I have my uropathy filter in case I get stranded somewhere
还得喝自己的尿
and have to drink my own pee.
我们已经尽力了。
We've done all we can.
记住，不要害怕任何事情。
Remember, don't be afraid of anything.
凡事都要害怕。
Be afraid of everything.
兔子在哪里?第一次拥抱是什么时候?
Where are the bunnies? And what time is the first cuddle?
我也喜欢兔子。
I love bunnies too.
他们是美味的。
They're delicious.
来吧,儿子。
Come on, son.
爸爸，我真的必须戴这个领结吗?
Dad, do I really have to wear this bow tie?
就像脖子上挂着"踢我"的牌子。
It's like wearing a "kick me" sign on my neck.
没有领结，你只是另一个魔术师。
Without that bow tie, you are just another magician.
但你是科尔内留斯·凯斯勒的儿子…神奇的皇室。
But you're Kornelius Kessler's son... Magic royalty.
记住，只有金魔杖才有用。
Now remember, nothing but the Golden Wand will do.
如果你需要我，我会在密苏里州的布兰森。
If you need me, I'll be in Branson, Missouri.
你父亲让我告诉你要好好玩。
Your father instructed me to tell you to have a good time.
他还要求我把这个给你。
He also asked that I give you this.
你妈妈让我给你这个。
And your mother asked that I give you this.
一,二。
One, two.
詹妮尔，和往常一样，我必须请求你
And, Janelle, as always, I must request,
既然是我来找你，
since I would be the one who would have to come find you,
请不要像在其他营地那样逃跑。
please don't run away like you have at so many other camps.
也许你可以试着参与进来。
Maybe you could even try to participate.
我不作任何承诺，汉密尔顿。
I make no promises, Hamilton.
也许我们可以试着让这种态度消失。
Maybe we can try and make that attitude disappear.
宝贝，安迪·达克曼回来了!
Andy Duckerman is back, baby!
-嘿，你去哪?我就在这里。——用黑木制作它!
- Hey, where you going? I'm right here. - It's Darkwood!
这就跟你问声好！你好吗?嗨。谢谢你！
Hi! How are you? Hi. Thank you.
嗨。嗨。你们喜欢魔术吗?
Hi. Hi. Do you guys like magic?
是啊!
Yeah!
我还得签到。
I still have to sign in.
我不知道我是否属于这里。我只是在房间里玩牌。
I don't know if I belong here. I just play with cards in my room.
我知道你很害怕
I know you're scared,
但要记住你最初来这里的原因。
but remember why you came in the first place.
亲爱的，我也想他。
Honey, I miss him too.
但让我问你一件事。
But let me ask you one thing.
你喜欢魔术吗?
Do you love magic?
我们能不能趁我还没被人逮到之前离开这里?
Can we get outta here before I get any geek on me?
别担心你的房间。
Don't worry about your room.
我不会同时有超过十个朋友在那里。
I'll never have more than ten friends in there at one time.
传说许多年前，
Legend holds that many years ago,
罗伊·普雷斯顿，世界上最重要的…不，检查一下，最多五张
Roy Preston, the world's foremost... No, check that, five-most
踢踏舞魔术师就消失在这个建筑里了
tap dancing magician disappeared in this very building
如果你大声尖叫，他可能会再次出现。
and that if you scream very loud, he might reappear.
欢迎来到罗伊·普雷斯顿的史前剧院。
Welcome to Roy Preston's Prememorial Theater.
你能为我鼓掌两次吗?
Can you clap twice for me?
你会跺脚吗?
Can you stomp your feet?
现在分解一下。是的。
Now break it down. Yeah.
其他人是怎么知道的?
How does everyone else know this?
布拉沃。布拉沃。很好。
Bravo. Bravo. Very good.
欢迎来到学院的最后一届夏季课程。
Welcome to the last summer session of the institute.
这个夏天你要竭尽全力
This summer you're gonna do your best,
那你就会做得更好。
then you're gonna do better than your best.
还有比最好中的最好中最好的小木屋
And the cabin that does better than the best of the best of the best
在我们最后的表演中
at our final performance
将赢得梦寐以求的礼帽奖
will win the coveted Top Hat award.
对于这个被认为是最杰出的年轻魔术师来说……
And for the young magician who is deemed to be the most exceptional...
哇。
Whoa.
黄金棒。
The Golden Wand.
——哇。——喔。
- Whoa. - Whoo.
我已经赢了三场。
I've won three.
现在在这段自我发现和魔法掌握的旅程中指导你
Now guiding you on this journey of self-discovery and magical mastery
都是当今最优秀的魔术师。
are some of the finest magicians working today.
带领黑桃舱，薛西斯!
Leading the Spades cabin, Xerxes!
欢迎来到一个下雪的夏天。
Welcome to a summer of snow.
哇。
Whoa.
现在，俱乐部的领导，莉娜·兰伯特!
And now, leader of the Clubs, Lena Lambert!
谁敢喝魔法杯?
Who dares drink from the goblet of magic?
令人毛骨悚然的。
Spooky.
哇。
Whoa.
哇!
Whoa!
哇。
Whoa.
下一位魔术师无需介绍
Our next magician needs no introduction
但她是钻石之王，克里斯汀娜·达伍德!
except she's the leader of the Diamonds, Kristina Darkwood!
唵嘛呢叭咪吽,微小的人类。
Abracadabra, tiny humans.
哇。
Whoa.
很明显,这是电线。请。
It's wires, obviously. Please.
我看到你。我知道你的希望。
I see you. I know your hopes.
你梦想成为谁?告诉你的邻居。
Who do you dream of being? Tell your neighbor.
在他耳边说。
Whisper it in his ear.
它是……
Was it...
尼克乔纳斯?
Nick Jonas?
嗯,这是错误的。
Um, that's wrong.
我梦想成为乔纳斯·索尔克，而不是乔纳斯兄弟。
I dreamed of being Jonas Salk, not a Jonas brother.
——谁?-你确定吗?
- Who? - Are you sure?
尼克·乔纳斯超级可爱。你可能会迷失在那双眼睛里。
Nick Jonas is super cute. You could get lost in those eyes.
嗯，是的，他很帅。但很抱歉，我说乔纳斯·索尔克。
Um, yes, he is very handsome. But I'm sorry, I said Jonas Salk.
小儿麻痹症疫苗的发明者。
Inventor of the polio vaccine.
教父的抗生素。
Godfather of antibiotics.
我的绝地大师。
My Jedi Master.
我很抱歉。这是尴尬的。
I'm sorry. This is awkward.
也许别人夺走了你的梦想。
Maybe someone else took your dream.
你!先生,打扰一下!
You! Sir, excuse me!
我想你可能无意中带走了这个小男孩的梦想。
I think you may have accidentally taken this young boy's dream.
不。我没有带走一个孩子的梦想。
No. I didn't take a child's dream.
我以为我们都知道这个房间里只有一个偷梦的人。
Think we all know there's only one dream stealer in this room.
检查你的口袋里。
Check your pocket.
不可能。
No way.
乔纳斯·索尔克。
Jonas Salk.
魔法。
Magic.
不，这不是魔法。这只是统计数据。真的。
No, it's not magic. It's just statistics. Really.
82%的人说“乔纳斯·索尔克”。
Eighty-two percent of people say "Jonas Salk."
太酷了，她在这里当辅导员。
It's so cool she's a counselor here.
为我们最后的顾问，心灵的领袖…
For our last counselor, leader of the Hearts...
大卫布莱恩?
David Blaine?
——大卫·布莱恩?没有办法,真的吗?——嘿,嘿。
- David Blaine? No way, really? - Hey, hey.
-不是大卫·布莱恩——哦。
- It's, not David Blaine. - Aw.
但是代替他的是学院的一位传奇人物，
But in his place is one of the great institute legends,
一个令人难以置信的天才，他的工作是可以找到的
an incredible talent whose work can be found
整个拉斯维加斯大道，会议中心和当地机场，
all over the Vegas Strip and the convention center and local airports,
安迪Duckerman先生。
Mr. Andy Duckerman.
嘿。有什么事吗?我是安迪。
Hey. What's up? I'm Andy.
你愿意上台来吗?你想玩些把戏吗?
Would you like to come up on the stage? Would you like to do some tricks?
我甚至没有带任何把戏…要做的事情。
I didn't even bring any tricks... to do.
你知道吗?
You know what?
我不会耍小把戏，因为这是你们的舞台，伙计们。
I'm not gonna do a trick, because it's your stage, guys.
它不是我的。
It's not mine.
我也不偷孩子们的梦想，因为我没必要这么做。
And I don't steal children's dreams, 'cause I don't have to.
我赢过三次金魔杖。繁荣!
I've won the Golden Wand three times. Boom!
你知道吗?我要很快地抓住这些。
You know what? I'm gonna grab these real quick.
继续工作。伟大的东西。
Carry on. Great stuff.
-谢谢，安迪。——三次!
- Thank you, Andy. - Three times!
好了，是时候让你找到自己的路了
Okay, so it's time for you to find your way
回到你们指定的小木屋。
out back to your designated cabins.
我们怎么知道去哪里?
Um, how do we know where to go?
露丝，只有你才知道答案。
Ruth, only you hold that answer.
是的!钻石是最好的!
Yes! Diamonds are the best!
好消息。我们在一张床上。想分享我的加湿器吗?
Good news. We're in the same bunk. Wanna share my humidifier?
要么是这样，要么是斯蒂芬·库里的篮球训练营，
It was either this or basketball camp with Steph Curry,
但是妈妈说我这个夏天一定要玩得开心，所以我当然选择了这个。
but Mother said I had to have fun this summer, so of course I chose this.
——嘿,菜鸟。——“菜鸟”?
- Hey, noobs. - "Noobs"?
是的,像“新手”。比如"初来乍到" "不懂事"
Yeah, like "newbie." Like "new to camp," like "doesn't know the ropes."
没有“招式”。
Doesn't have the "moves."
这个名字是维克。在“胜利”。
The name's Vic. As in "victory."
去年金棒奖得主。
Last year's Golden Wand winner.
嘿。西奥。
Hey. Theo.
让我看看你怎么做。是时候欺骗受害者了。
Let me see you do a trick. Time to trick the Vic.
嗯,好吧。确定。
Um, okay. Sure.
嗯…
Um...
-选一张牌。任何卡。-我好像见过这个。
- Pick a card. Any card. - Think I've seen this one before.
我还没开始呢。
I haven't even started.
我只是在跟你开玩笑。
I'm just messing with ya.
继续，你做得很好。
Keep going, you're doing great.
我只是…嗯…
I just... Um...
好吧，我要拿走你的黑桃皇后然后…
Okay, I'm gonna take your queen of spades and...
别担心。只是新手的神经。让我告诉你怎么做。
Don't worry. Just noob nerves. Let me show you how it's done.
所以我有一个空杯子和一瓶水。
So I have an empty cup and a bottle of water.
我要把它倒在这里，这样你会看到一切都是合法的。
I'm gonna pour it in here just so you see everything's legit.
哦。
Ooh.
看看这个。
Check this out.
空的。哈!
Empty. Ta-da!
很酷，维克。
That was cool, Vic.
等等，还有一个部分。
Wait, but there's one more part to this trick.
那是不必要的。
That was uncalled for.
去和乔纳斯·索尔克私奔吧。
Go run away with Jonas Salk.
祝你创造dweeb疫苗好运!
Good luck creating a dweeb vaccine!
神奇的营地。即使是恶霸也是书呆子。
Magic camp. Even the bullies are nerds.
当国王真好。
It's good to be the king.
-你是最棒的!-非常感谢。
- You're the best ever! - Thank you so much.
-给你。——谢谢。
- Here you go. - Thank you.
我知道你在看我。我就在这里。
I know you see me. I'm right here.
克里斯蒂娜。我没看见你在那儿。
Kristina. I didn't see you there.
嗨,安迪。已经太久了。-我爱你，克里斯蒂娜!
- Hi, Andy. It's been too long. - I love you, Kristina!
我本来想说时间还不够长。
I was actually gonna say it hasn't been long enough.
——谢谢!-。嗯…
- Thank you! - . Well...
我真的很惊讶在这里见到你。我以为你放弃了魔法。
I was actually surprised to see you here. I thought you'd given up magic.
我爱你。
I love you.
说实话，我只是在帮普雷斯顿一个忙。代替大卫·布莱恩。
Honestly I'm just doing Preston a favor. Filling in for David Blaine.
克里斯蒂娜，你是最棒的。
Kristina, you're the greatest.
真有趣，因为普雷斯顿让我今年夏天接替大卫。
That's funny, 'cause Preston asked me to step in for David this summer.
你是否觉得他只是在抚摸你的自尊心?
Do you think maybe he's just stroking your ego a little bit?
我很高兴你能来。回馈社会是件好事。
I'm glad you're here. It's good to give back.
指导孩子，训练下一代…
Mentor kids, train the next generation...
在你最意想不到的时候在背后捅你一刀
To stab you in the back when you least expect it.
我真的希望，你知道，我们已经度过了这一切。
I really hoped that we were, you know, past all this.
我是。我很酷。我在做…老实说，我做得很好。
I am. I'm cool. I'm doing... I'm doing great, honestly.
在世界各地为超级重要人物举办私人演出。
Doing private shows around the world for super-important people.
这就是为什么你没见过我，没听说过我的演出。
It's why you haven't seen me around, why you haven't heard of my shows.
但我向你保证，薪水相当不错。
But I assure you, it pays quite well.
这就是为什么你用垃圾袋当行李的原因。
And that's why you're using garbage bags as luggage.
-这是环保的东西。-其实不是。
- It's a eco-friendly thing. - It's actually not.
无论什么。我只知道我的铺位会揍你
Whatever. All I know is that my bunk is gonna beat you
就像我们小时候每年夏天我都会做的那样。
just like I did every summer when we were kids.
——好。你在。——好。你在。
- Fine. You're on. - Fine. You're on.
不,你……我在做什么?
No, you're... What am I doing?
我们是为孩子们而来的。这是荒谬的。
We're here for the kids. This is ridiculous.
你知道什么是荒谬的吗?你会输得多惨。
You know what's ridiculous? How bad you're gonna lose.
好了。
Nice.
——是的。嗨,伙计们!
- Yes. - Hi, guys!
欢迎,钻石!进来吧。
Welcome, Diamonds! Come on in.
我是受害者，去年的金魔杖奖得主。
I'm the Vic, last year's Golden Wand winner.
好了。
Nice.
就像恐怖电影里的小屋。
It's like a cabin from a horror movie.
——电子战。恶心。-就像一个巨大的碎片。
- Ew. Gross. - It's like one giant splinter.
啊,男人。我忘了带破伤风助推器了。
Aw, man. I forgot my tetanus booster.
那个浑身湿透的孩子在哪儿?
Hey, where's the kid that got all wet?
这是好的,西奥。这儿有一件干衬衫。
It's okay, Theo. Here's a dry shirt.
谢谢。
Thanks.
真不敢相信克里斯汀娜·达克伍德今年夏天会当辅导员。
I can't believe Kristina Darkwood is a counselor this summer.
我听说她像我们这么大的时候是个十足的呆子
I heard when she was our age she was a total dork,
但后来她变得非常擅长魔术，变得超级有名。
but then she got really good at magic and became super famous.
是的，我想我们都在祈祷这个故事。
Yeah, I think we're all crossing our fingers for that narrative.
你们在说Dorkwood吗?
You guys talking about Dorkwood?
是啊，她在这里露营的时候我们就是这么叫她的。
Yeah, that's what we used to call her when she was a camper here.
克里斯蒂娜Dorkwood。
Kristina Dorkwood.
她从来没有连续三年赢得过金魔杖，但你知道是谁赢得的吗?
She never won the Golden Wand three years in a row, but you know who did?
——大卫·布莱恩?——没有。
- David Blaine? - No.
事实上，是的，他做到了。但我也是。
Actually, yes, he did. But so did I.
每次都是我赢，而克里斯汀娜都输给了我。
I won, and Kristina lost every time to me.
所以，你们应该庆幸和我在一起，而不是和她在一起。
So, you should consider yourselves lucky that you ended up with me and not her.
你还在表演吗?
Do you still perform?
是的。在世界各地的私人演出中
Yep. In private shows all over the world.
我从没听说过你的独唱生涯
I've never heard of your solo career,
我对过去和现在的魔术师都有广博的了解。
and I have an encyclopedic knowledge of magicians both past and present.
我在谷歌上搜索了你。你的名字只和克里斯汀娜·达伍德有关…
And I googled you. Your name only comes up connected to Kristina Darkwood...
真的吗?让我看看。
Really? Let me see that.
哇。
Whoa.
酷。它是如何重现的?
Cool. How does it reappear?
它不是。直到夏天的最后一天。
It doesn't. Not until the last day of summer.
——营地规则。——“没有电话。”
- Camp rules. - "No phones."
我们来这里不是要谈论我的神奇而又超级秘密的职业生涯。
And we're not here to talk about my amazing and super-secret career.
我们来这里是为了赢得礼帽和金魔杖。
We're here to win the Top Hat and the Golden Wand.
让我来见见普雷斯顿赋予我的年轻天才。
So let me meet the young talent Preston has gifted me with.
你。你叫什么名字?你的专业是什么?
You. What is your name? What is your specialty?
我叫Ruth Brusselbach，我的专长是兔女郎。
My name is Ruth Brusselbach, and my specialty is bunnies.
我不知道那是什么意思。
I don't know what that means.
严格地说，我从来没有和它共事过，
Technically, I've never worked with one,
但是自从我看到魔术师从帽子里变出兔子后，
but ever since I saw a magician pull a rabbit out of a hat,
我知道这是我的命运。
I knew it was my destiny.
-什么时候会发生?-明天第一件事。
- So when does that happen? - First thing tomorrow.
——是的。-你呢?你的交易是什么?
- Yes. - What about you? What's your deal?
我是凯斯勒贾德。
I'm Judd Kessler.
和科尔内留斯·凯斯勒有关系吗?
Any relation to Kornelius Kessler?
我爸爸。
My dad.
这就是你戴领结的原因!就像你爸爸的一样。
That's why you're wearing the bow tie! It's just like your dad's.
是的，这不是我的第一选择。
Yeah, it's not my first choice of accessory.
这家伙的爸爸?活着的传奇。
This guy's dad? Living legend.
这一定会使你成为一个神奇的纯种马。
That must make you a magic thoroughbred.
我不确定魔法是怎么起作用的。
I'm not sure that's how magic works.
这更多是一种隐性基因，比如眼睛颜色或血型。
It's more of a recessive gene like eye color or blood type.
不要害羞。给我看些东西。
Don't be shy. Show me somethin'.
听着，我只是想告诉你我不知道怎么做杂志…
Look, I'm just trying to tell you that I don't know how to do mag...
我不用担心你。你可以在早上给我看。
I don't have to worry about you. You can show me in the morning.
”凯。
'Kay.
仙特克，你有戏法要给我看吗?
Zyrtec, you got a trick you wanna show me?
那其实是我的Zyrtec衬衫。大风扇。
That's actually my Zyrtec shirt. Big fan.
嗯,我的弟弟。
Um, I'm Theo.
嗯，也不完全是。
And, um, not really.
它不需要是一个新的把戏。就是你去年夏天学到的东西。
It doesn't need to be a new trick. Just anything you learned last summer.
这实际上是我在这里的第一年。
This is actually my first year here.
——是的。我也是。——我也是。
- Yep. Me too. - Me too.
你们都是新手?
You're all newbies?
是的。
Yeah.
普雷斯顿。
Preston.
蒂娜,Zozo,亚历克斯。
Tina, Zozo, Alex.
哇。真的很喜欢这个小兔子。
Wow. Really committed to this bunny thing.
兔子爱不是“东西”。这是一种生活方式。
Bunny love is not a "thing." It's a way of life.
就像一个武士…只有更多的兔子。
Like being a samurai... only with more bunnies.
好吧。
Okay.
嘿，我忘了问。你专业是什么?
Hey, I forgot to ask. What's your specialty?
我不确定。卡,我猜。
I'm not sure. Cards, I guess.
你在申请表上写了什么?
What did you put on your application?
我不知道。我爸爸填的。
I don't know. My dad filled it out.
明白了。再次感谢你让我睡下铺。
Gotcha. And thanks again for letting me take the bottom bunk.
正如我之前提到的，我是一个喜欢在晚上撒尿的人。和梦游。
As I mentioned before, I'm a bit of a night pee-er. And sleepwalker.
不幸的是，并不总是按照这个顺序。
Unfortunately, not always in that order.
有时，我无缘无故地在半夜尖叫着醒来。
And sometimes, for no reason, I wake up in the middle of the night screaming.
早上4点见。
Welp, see you at 4:00 a.m.
好了,伙计们。熄灯。大的明天。
Okay, guys. Lights out. Big day tomorrow.
你得证明给我看，我不是在浪费时间。
You get to prove to me that I'm not wasting my time here.
Alaka-zip-it。
Alaka-zip-it.
太酷了!
Cool!
我认为他不太喜欢我们。
I don't think he likes us very much.
他用垃圾袋当行李。很明显，他甚至不喜欢自己。
He uses trash bags as luggage. He clearly doesn't even like himself.
人吗?我能听见。我就在这里。
Guys? I can hear you. I'm right here.
选择一个卡。记住它。
Pick a card. Memorize it.
把它放回去。
Put it back.
好吧。现在，把你的卡放在中间，对吗?
Okay. Now, you put your card in the middle, right?
是的。
Yeah.
那它是怎么重新出现在顶部的呢?
Then how come it reappeared at the top?
哇。你是怎么做到的?
Whoa. How did you do that?
魔术师从不泄露他的秘密。
A magician never reveals his secrets.
但如果我把这些卡片给你，我就可以教你。
But if I give these cards to you, then I can teach you.
早上好,露营者。
Good morning, campers.
离高帽比赛还有34天。
Thirty-four days until the Top Hat competition.
是时候关注一些骗局了。
Time to focus on some hocus-pocus.
午餐是红酱意大利面。
Lunch will be spaghetti in red sauce.
逃脱是每个真正魔术师的武器库的基本元素。
Escape is a fundamental element in every true magician's arsenal.
所以我们要做最基本的逃跑。
So we're gonna be doing the most basic of escapes.
手被绑在前面。非常容易。
Hands tied in front. Very easy.
听着，我刚刚做到了。好吧，我们试试。
Look, I just did it. Okay, let's try it.
好的，用手在结的背面摩擦。的背。
Okay, rub your hands on the back of the knot. On the back.
不要咬它。不要咬它。
Do not bite it. Do not bite it.
这不是背面。那是完全不对的。
That is not the back. That is not right at all.
-后面的ha…-谁来帮帮我!
- Back of the ha... - Somebody help me!
什么?哇，你怎么做到的…
What? Wow, how did you do...
这是非常错误的，但我对此印象深刻。
That is very wrong, but I'm impressed by that.
我的大腿麻了。
Can't feel my thigh.
好吧，让我们试试更简单的方法。
Okay, let's try something simpler.
近景魔术。
Close-up magic.
这被称为假转移。
This is called a false transfer.
你以为我把它放在左手里了吗?
You think I put it in my left hand.
这是我的权利。
It's in my right.
好吧?让我们试一试。
Okay? Let's try it.
坏的。非常糟糕。
Bad. Very bad.
坏的。
Bad.
内特，那很好。
Nate, that's pretty good.
卡在我喉咙里了。
It's stuck in my throat.
等等，你是认真的吗?有人知道海姆利克急救法吗?
Wait, are you serious? Does anyone know the Heimlich?
没有?护士!
No? Nurse!
欢迎来到操控庄园。
Okay, welcome to manipulation manor.
显然，蓬松的红球太复杂了，
Obviously, fluffy red balls are too complicated,
所以让我们来做一些基本的动物处理。
so let's work on some basic animal handling.
甚至与魔法无关，只是简单的宠物-动物园级别的交互。
Not even magic-related, just simple petting-zoo-level interactions.
哈!那臭鼬的名字叫弗雷德。
Ha! That skunk's name is Fred.
这是疯狂的有趣。
That's crazy funny.
这里的56只动物都由一个人照管吗?
Does one person care for all 56 animals here?
-有多少动物?-是的。
- Is that how many animals there are? - Yeah.
——是的。-你怎么知道的?
- Yes. - How'd you know that?
——这是显而易见的。——人!
- It's obvious. - Guys!
谁在乎有多少动物?
Who cares how many animals there are?
为什么这些可爱的兔子和那些可怕的鸟和蛇在一起?
Why are these adorable bunnies next to those horrifying birds and snakes?
更重要的是,
And more importantly,
为什么现在兔子不在我手里?
why aren't the bunnies in my hands right now?
是的,露丝。好吧。
Yes, Ruth. All right.
自从你来到这里，你就一直在说兔子
All you've talked about since you got here are bunnies,
所以在你的第一个不可能搞砸的练习中，
so for your first impossible-to-mess-up exercise,
我只希望你…兔子。
I want you to simply... hold the bunny.
你为什么哭?
Why are you crying?
它只是那么…可爱。
It's just so... cute.
它实际上伤害了。
It actually hurts.
我受不了了。可爱的疼。
I can't stand it. The cuteness hurts.
把它放回去。把它放回去!你不敢把它放回去。
Put it back. Put it back! Don't you dare put it back.
早上好,露营者。
Good morning, campers.
离高帽比赛还有28天。
Twenty-eight days until the Top Hat competition.
继续训练。
Keep at your training.
今天的午餐很特别…
And today's lunch is a special treat...
吃剩的热狗，由拉斯维加斯Weiners World提供。
Leftover hot dogs, courtesy of World Of Weiners, Las Vegas.
好,伙计们。很神奇的。
Great job, guys. Amazing.
为什么安迪不那样教我们?
Why doesn't Andy teach us like that?
为什么每个人都有自己的机舱t恤呢?
And why does everyone else get their own cabin T-shirts?
伙计，我们就差这么一点点就有大卫·布莱恩了。
Man, we were this close to having David Blaine.
伙计们，就在这里。
Guys, again, right here.
太好了。你在整个营地的第一个魔术。
Great. Your first magic trick of the whole camp.
对吧?
Right?
你想把它折断。
You wanna snap it.
好吧，我想见你们。
All right, I wanna see you guys.
确保你的手腕有后续动作。好吧,那是更好的。
Make sure you have follow-through with your wrist. Okay, that's better.
普雷斯顿,可以…
Preston, can...
我们能不能现在不谈这个?
Can we not do this right now?
我知道你在这里，普雷斯顿。
I know you're in here, Preston.
躲在活板门或隐蔽的角落里，
Hiding in some trapdoor or hidden corner,
等着我转过身，你就会奇迹般地出现，对我说，
waiting for me to turn around so you can magically appear and say,
-“我一直都在这里。”-一直都是。
- "I've been right here the whole time." - the whole time.
完全正确。你这么可以预测的。
Exactly. You're so predictable.
-有什么问题吗?-问题出在你给我的铺位上
- What's the problem? - The bunk that you gave me is the problem.
这些孩子，普雷斯顿，他们都是新来的。他们没有任何技能。
These kids, Preston, they're all newbies. They have zero skills.
现在，你明白了，这是一个为想学魔术的孩子们准备的训练营，
Now, you understand that this is a camp for children who wanna learn magic,
而你是来教他们的。
and you're here to teach them.
普雷斯顿，这些孩子，他们没救了。
Preston, these kids, they're hopeless.
内森被海绵球噎住了。
Nathan choked on a sponge ball.
露丝连一只兔子都不敢碰。她喜欢兔子。
Ruth can't even touch a bunny. And she loves bunnies.
他们甚至连最基本的纸牌把戏都玩不出来。
They can't even pull off the most basic card trick.
但是你看，一个你不相信的把戏是把戏，
But you see, a trick that you don't believe is a trick,
这是最好的技巧。
that's the best trick of all.
这就是你要给我的建议?
That's the advice you're gonna give me?
只是一些普通的魔法谚语
Just more generic magical proverbs
这听起来很有意义，但完全是无稽之谈?
that sound meaningful but are total nonsense?
安迪，只有这样才能创造更多的魔法
Andy, the only way to create more magic in the world
不是通过创造更多的魔法。
is not by creating more magic.
——是的。就像这样。-安迪，让我说完
- Yep. Just like that. - Andy, let me finish.
-不，我受够了。——这是…
- No, I'm done. - It's...
对不起，普雷斯顿，我受够了。我离开这里。好吧?
I'm sorry, Preston, but I'm done. I'm outta here. Okay?
愚蠢的。
Stupid.
我做得很好。
I was doing perfectly fine.
嗯,不是很好。我在做好事。good-ish。排序的。
Well, not great. I was doing good. Was doing good-ish. Sort of.
我可能错了，
I could be mistaken,
但我记得我看到过一个12岁的孩子用一只手完美地跳法罗牌。
but I think I saw a 12-year-old execute a perfect faro shuffle with one hand.
我只是在鬼混。
I was just fooling around.
法罗洗牌是单手最难的纸牌技巧之一，
A faro shuffle is one of the single most difficult card skills with two hands,
我想你们只是用了一个。
and you just did it with one, I think.
-再来一次。-我不想。
- Do it again. - I don't want to.
——为什么不呢?你做到了。-我害怕。
- Why not? You just did it. - I get scared.
-怕什么?-我不知道。人们看着我。
- Scared of what? - I don't know. People looking at me.
无论如何,很愚蠢。只是…
Anyway, it's stupid. Just...
你知道那是什么吗?
You know what that is?
这就是怯场。
That is stage fright.
进入你的脑海。对于一个魔术师来说，这是一个怪异的地方。
Gets in your head. And that is a freaky place for a magician to be.
-你以前也这样吗?——没有。别荒谬。
- It's happened to you before? - No. Don't be ridiculous.
虽然，我是一个受欢迎的专业人士。
Although, I am an acclaimed professional.
而你，在另一方面，是一个可以做完美的法罗洗牌的业余选手。
You, on the other hand, are a rank amateur who can somehow do a perfect faro shuffle.
让我看看。
So let me see it.
-就像我说的…-假装我不在这里。别看我。
- Like I said... - Pretend I'm not here. Don't look at me.
保持洗牌。保持牌的移动。好吧?
Keep shuffling. Keep the cards moving. Okay?
你从哪里来?
So where you from?
兰开斯特,加州。
Lancaster, California.
这听起来……
That sounds...
实际上，这听起来很无聊。我不会骗你的。
That sounds boring, actually. I'm not gonna lie to you.
没关系。可能有点无聊。
It's okay. Maybe a little boring.
我们住在爱德华兹空军基地附近。很多军人家庭。
We live near Edwards Air Force Base. Lot of military families.
你爸爸在服役吗?
Is your dad in the service?
他是。
He was.
这些是他的卡片。
Um, these were his cards.
嘿!你有兄弟姐妹吗?
Hey! Do you have any brothers or sisters?
我有个小弟弟叫卡梅隆。他是最坏的打算。
I have a little brother named Cameron. He's the worst.
——超级烦人吗?——是的,完全。
- Super annoying? - Yeah, totally.
老兄,你很棒。让我看看你的套路。
Dude, you're great. Show me your routine.
好吧。拿张卡就行了。
Okay. Um, just take a card.
好吧。
All right.
现在帮我把它放在最上面。
Now put it on top for me.
好吧。
Okay.
,嗯…
And, um...
嘿,放松。
Hey, relax.
只有你和我。
It's just you and me.
好吧,再试一次。
Okay, try again.
放松。
Relax.
只有你和我。
It's just you and me.
好，方块3。
Okay, three of diamonds.
“凯?把它放进去。
'Kay? Just gonna put that in there.
-现在你能帮我把它塞进去吗?——确定。
- Now can you just tuck it in for me? - Sure.
这是你的卡吗?
Is this your card?
我的上帝,西奥!
My God, Theo!
你是惊人的。
You are amazing.
不，我只是知道一些技巧。
Nah, I just know some tricks.
不，你是个魔术师。
No, you are a magician.
——谢谢。-我能搞定的。
- Thanks. - I can work with this.
可惜你的同屋都没用。
Too bad your bunkmates are so useless.
内森是个数字天才，而贾德知道很多…
Nathan is a genius with numbers, and Judd knows a lot about...
我们现在得去你的铺位好好谈谈。我们走吧。来吧。
We need to have a little talk with your bunk right now. Let's go. Come on.
伙计们,嘿。
Guys, hey.
如果我告诉你我们至少有机会了呢
What if I told you we have at least some semblance of a shot
赢得高顶帽比赛?
to win the Top Hat competition?
我得说我的血糖非常低。
I'd say my blood sugar is really low.
不,我是认真的。西奥显然是个秘密红衣主教
No, I'm serious. Theo is apparently a secret Cardini,
他告诉我，你们没有我想的那么烂。
and he tells me that you guys don't suck half as bad as I thought.
我觉得很难相信，但别把他当成骗子。
Which I find hard to believe, but let's not make a liar out of him.
你是在耍我们是在惩罚我们对魔法的精通吗?
Are you messing with us as a punishment for being awful at magic?
我是认真的。作为三次金棒冠军和…
I'm serious. As a three-time Golden Wand winner and...
等待。你赢得了金魔杖?
Wait. You won the Golden Wand?
我们听到。现在我们可以吃饭了吗?
We've heard. Now can we eat?
-马上。我解决你。-你能在我们吃饭的时候称呼我们吗?
- In a second. I'm addressing you. - Can you address us while we eat?
不,不。这整个激动人心的演讲是我先想象出来的。
No, no. I had envisioned this whole rousing speech thing first.
在你教我们之前，你不能做所有的振奋人心的演讲。
You don't get to do the whole rousing speech thing until you teach us stuff.
好吧,公平点。但请听我说完。
Okay, fair point. But hear me out.
如果我们能找到你不太臭的地方，
If we can find the areas where you don't totally stink,
我可以把你们训练成像样的魔术师。
I can train you to be sort of decent magicians.
有了西奥的技术，我们也许能打败黑木队。
And with Theo's skills, we might actually be able to beat Darkwood.
我的意思是，赢得高顶帽比赛!
I mean, win the Top Hat competition!
我是谁?
Who's with me?
好了，这就是你们开始说“安迪!安迪!”
Okay, this is where you guys start going, "Andy! Andy!"
如果我们说好，我们能吃吗?
If we say yes, can we eat?
——是的!——好的。
- Yes! - Okay.
——最后。-加油吧。我们有工作要做。
- Finally. - Let's fuel up. We got work to do.
走向我。
Walk towards me.
不要太僵硬，好吗?自然地行走。
Not so stiff, okay? Walk naturally.
握住你的手，就好像你的手是空的。
Hold your hands as if they're actually empty.
现在它们实际上是空的。来吧,伙计们。这是手掌101。
Now they are actually empty. Come on, guys. This is Palming 101.
内森，别告诉我你对Tsum过敏。
Nathan, don't tell me you're allergic to Tsum Tsums.
不。但我对灰尘过敏。
No. But I'm allergic to dirt.
好了，伙计们，我们要让紧身衣更上一层楼。
Okay, guys, we are taking it to the next level with straitjackets.
你知道，这真的很好。有点像拥抱。
You know, this is nice, actually. It's kind of like a hug.
-是的，不是吗?-嘿，安迪，你能帮我再申请一次吗?
- It is, isn't it? - Hey, Andy, could you reapply for me?
是的。是啊，我抓住你了，伙计。
Yeah. Yeah, I got you, bud.
——谢谢。-告诉我什么时候。
- Thank you. - Tell me when.
这很好。
That's good.
——你好吗?——是的。
- You good? - Yes.
-这不可能。-不，不是。
- This is impossible. - No, it isn't.
胡迪尼曾经说过:“我的大脑是让我获得自由的钥匙。”
Houdini once said, "My brain is the key that sets me free."
胡迪尼爱尔兰吗?
Was Houdini Irish?
不，他是匈牙利人。那是个坏印象。
No, he was Hungarian. That was a bad impression.
好了，完全呼气，然后用这个放松的时间将手臂一直伸到后面。
Okay, exhale fully, then use that slack to reach your arm all the way back.
喔!
Whoo.
好吧!现在你明白了。高5。
All right! Now you're getting it. High five.
当然可以。
Of course.
——哦。-那是我的错。
- Ooh. - That is my bad.
是的!
Yes!
现在我可以和兔子们一起工作了吗?
Now do I get to work with the bunnies?
露丝，你还没准备好做兔子呢。
Ruth, you are nowhere near bunny-ready.
你为什么要这样搅乱我的情绪?
Why are you messing with my emotions like this?
在你跑之前，你得学会爬。
Well, before you run, you gotta learn how to crawl.
这让我想到……海龟。
Which leads me to... the turtles.
又小又慢，就像你们一样。来吧，拿一个。
Tiny and slow, just like you guys. Go ahead, grab one.
兔子桩!我准备好拥抱了!
Bunny pile! I'm ready for my cuddles!
到我这里来，我的朋友们!
Come to me, my friends!
得到他们!很快!
Get 'em! Quickly!
露丝!不!
Ruth! No!
-把乌龟扔了。——回来!
- Drop the turtles. - Come back!
——不!他们得到了!-你要去哪里?
- No! They're getting out! - Where are you going?
在盒子里。抓住一只兔子!每个人，每个人，快抓住他们。
In the box. Grab a bunny! Everybody, everybody, just get 'em.
-你要去哪里?-去拿兔子!
- Where are you going? - Get the bunnies!
呼气放松。把你的胳膊举过肩膀。
Exhale to create some slack. Get your arm up over your shoulder.
让他们离水远点!
Keep 'em away from the water!
在那里!
Over there!
人失望!
Man down!
好吧，这是一个我们不用担心大礼帽的小屋。
Well, that's one cabin we don't have to worry about for Top Hat.
维克，我怎么跟你说的?是一个好去处。
Vic, what did I tell you? Be nice.
停止那些兔子!
Stop those bunnies!
——电子战。恶心。——得到他们!
- Ew. Gross. - Get 'em!
——在那里!-是啊，我刚才尖叫了。
- Over there! - Yeah, I just screamed that.
-注意你的紧身衣。-他们要跑了!
- Concentrate on your straitjackets. - They're getting away!
——詹妮尔在哪?——可怜的。抓兔子。
- Where's Janelle? - Pathetic. Grab the bunny.
你为什么要逃避我?
Why are you running from me?
我有一个!
I got one!
——等待。不,我没有……-在灌木丛下面!
- Wait. No, I didn't... - Under the bush!
明白了!
Gotcha!
不,不要!
No, don't go!
我只是在找跑掉的兔子。
I'm just looking for the bunnies that got away.
-我看起来像兔子吗?——什么?不。
- Do I look like a bunny? - What? No.
嗯，可能有一点。我是说，像兔子一样可爱。
Well, maybe a little. I mean, like, cute like a bunny.
嗯,不是cute-cute。并不是说你不可爱。
Well, not cute-cute. Not that you're not cute.
他不肯骗受害人，所以我把他的手机塞进了一大口。
He wouldn't trick the Vic, so I palmed his phone into a Big Gulp.
你是怎么弄到钻石的?你看起来不错。
How'd you get with the Diamonds anyway? You seem nice.
我父母可能为我和黑木乐队在一起付了额外的钱。
My parents probably paid extra for me to be with Darkwood.
他们真是太酷了。
That's pretty cool of them.
他们并不是想耍酷。
They're not trying to be cool.
他们只是不想让我妨碍他们繁忙的工作。
They just don't want me getting in the way of their busy work schedule.
-嘿，那是詹妮尔吗?-是的。
- Hey, is that Janelle? - Yeah.
-她太奇怪了。-我得走了。
- She's so weird. - Um, I gotta bounce.
我看见你脱下了紧身衣。你是怎么做到的?
I saw you get out of that straitjacket. How did you do that?
我不知道。只是好玩。
I don't know. It's just fun.
就像你对你的身体做的拼图，我猜。
Like a puzzle you do with your body, I guess.
好了，现在我真的得走了。
Okay, now I really gotta go.
顺便说一下，我叫詹妮尔。
I'm Janelle, by the way.
西奥。
Theo.
离高顶礼帽还有17天。
Seventeen days until Top Hat.
午餐是砂锅菜。
Lunch will be casserole.
目前还不清楚是哪种类型。
It is unclear what kind.
这就是我们所说的法式降酒。你看到了什么?
This is what we call the French drop. You see?
你得保护角度不让观众看到。
You got to protect the angle from the audience.
——噢,噢。-好吧，你们试试看。
- Ooh, ooh. - All right, you guys try.
令人惊讶的是，这并不可怕，露丝。
That was surprisingly not terrible, Ruth.
谢谢你,安迪。
Thanks, Andy.
干得好,安迪。
Attaboy, Andy.
看来你们一直在听我精彩的教学。
Seems like you guys have been listening to my amazing teaching after all.
魔术并不是一种有氧运动。
Magic isn't exactly a cardio workout.
你的父母坚持让你在这个夏天进行体育锻炼
Your parents are insisting we try to get you some physical activity this summer,
所以…看起来有生机。
so... look alive.
好的,锻炼结束了!回到魔法!
Okay, workout over! Back to magic!
消失……和外观!
Vanish... and appearance!
哇。好工作。
Wow. Good job.
好吧，我想我们该进入下一个阶段了。
Okay, I think it's time we take things to the next level.
哇!
Whoa!
什么?我说我想和兔子一起工作，
What? I said I wanted to work with bunnies,
不是那些可怕的，会飞的便便机。
not those terrifying, flying poop-machines.
鲁斯，你解放了所有的兔子，
Well, Ruth, you liberated all of the bunnies,
这就是我们要解决的问题。
so this is what we have to work with.
举起你的手指。
Raise out your finger.
鸽子就像会飞的兔子。
Doves are like flying bunnies.
它们是魔术师情感的延伸。
They're an extension of a magician's emotions.
如果你自信，那就是自信。如果你紧张……
If you're confident, it's confident. If you're nervous...
哇!
Whoa!
然后发生的事情。
Then that happens.
很明显，这也是事实。
And apparently so does that.
好的,心。
Okay, Hearts.
我想你已经准备好聆听魔术界最大的秘密之一了。
I think you're ready to hear one of the biggest secrets in all of magic.
每个伟大魔术师的背后，都有……
Behind every great magician, there is...
一个更好的裁缝。
An even better tailor.
——好。那件运动外套真棒。
- Nice. - That sports coat is amazing.
贾德，我感觉到人们对服装的热情了吗?
Judd, am I sensing an enthusiasm for costumes?
欢迎来到服装设计的奇妙世界。
Welcome to the fabulous world of costume design.
如果你不介意的话，我想今天剩下的时间我还是在这里度过吧。
Think I'm gonna spend the rest of the day here, if that's cool with you.
露丝，也许你需要大点的。
Ruth, maybe you just need something bigger.
伊森，她不是食物，好吗?
Now, Ethan, she's not food, okay?
哇。
Whoa.
鹰现在是我的最爱了。
Hawks are my thing now.
鸟儿喜欢绿色。这就像……你就像一棵树。
Birds love the color green. It's like... It's like you're a tree.
好吧，跟我来。
All right, come with me.
嗨,爸爸。我有一个新把戏。
Hey, Dad. I got a new trick.
我现在不行，西奥。我赶不上飞机了。
I-I can't right now, Theo. I'm late for my flight.
-为你妈妈做。-妈妈不喜欢魔法。好吗?
- Do it for your mom. - Mom's not into magic. Please?
-是的。好吧。好吧。——好的。
- Yeah. Okay. Okay. - All right.
选择一个卡。
Pick a card.
好了。
There we go.
好吧。别让我看这是红桃j。
All right. Now don't let me see it's the jack of hearts.
好吧。
Okay.
这很好。你怎么知道的?
That's pretty good. How'd you know?
因为那是我。我是红心j。
'Cause that's me. I'm the jack of hearts.
和…这是你的。
And... that's you.
-你是红心之王。-你是怎么做到的…
- You're the king of hearts. - How did you do...
这是难以置信的。你是不可思议的,西奥。
That's incredible. You're incredible, Theo.
西奥。西奥。
Theo. Theo.
听着，每个人的行为都在成形，但我们都还没有。
Look, everyone's acts are shaping up, but neither of us have one yet.
所以我想我们可以组成一个魔术喜剧二人组
So I was thinking we could form a magical comedy duo
与我做勇敢的玩笑，而你wow每个人与你的卡魔术。
with me doing plucky banter while you wow everyone with your card magic.
我读到过放屁的声音很能取悦大众。
I've read that fart sounds are quite the crowd-pleaser.
你再偷偷给我一点奶酪，我就把这个地方的屋顶炸飞。
You sneak me even a bit of cheese, and I will blow the roof off this place.
-内特，千万别在人群上放屁——好的。
- Nate, definitely don't fart on the crowd. - Okay.
你们为什么不工作?演出在下周举行。
Why aren't you guys working? The show's next week.
我还在努力学习我的专业。
I'm still trying to figure out my specialty.
是的，这是个棘手的问题。
Yeah, that is a tricky one.
内特，这个电影院有几张票?
Hey, Nate, how many seats are in this theater?
273. 为什么?
273. Why?
为什么?因为你这么快就能做到。
Why? Because it's freakish how quickly you could do that.
你有别人没有的特别的东西。
You've got something special that no one else has.
突出的尾骨实际上比你想象的更常见。
A protruding tailbone is actually more common than you'd expect.
他说的是你计算东西的方式。
He's talking about the way you do your counting stuff.
是的，我只是数。我数，组，乘，还有…
Yeah, I just count. I count and group and multiply and...
这是魔法。
That's magic.
你的大脑就像一个巨大的、怪异的魔法计算器。
Your brain is like a big, weird magic calculator.
你可能是个唯心论者。
You could be a mentalist.
喜欢用黑木制作克里斯吗?
Like Kris Darkwood?
比克里斯·多克伍德还好。
Better than Kris Dorkwood.
-我需要坐下来——你。
- I need to sit down. - You are.
很好。
Very nice.
看上去不错,伙计们。哇!
Looking good, guys. Whoo!
-安迪，过来。——好的。
- Andy, come here. - Okay.
哇。
Whoa.
是的。
Yep.
——好。是的!-看起来不错。
- Good. Yes! - That looked so good.
西奥，让我们看看你的本事。
Okay, Theo, show us what you got.
——难以置信。-好吧，我们休息十分钟。
- Unbelievable. - Okay, let's take ten.
伙计们，继续练习你的小指。
You guys, keep working on your pinky break.
内森，让你的小指休息一下。
Nathan, give your pinky a break.
-那是痒，不是刺。我发誓。-好吧，很好。
- It was an itch, not a pick. I swear. - Okay, yeah, cool, all right.
伙计，怎么回事?你还在你的脑子里。
Dude, what's going on? You're still in your head.
你知道吗?跟我来。有些东西你需要看。
You know what? Follow me. There's something you need to see.
来吧。
Come on.
普雷斯顿的秘密图书馆。
Preston's secret library.
当我像你这么大的时候，他把我带到这里。
He took me here when I was about your age.
他说只有真正杰出的魔术师才能参加。
He said it was for only truly exceptional magicians.
去看看吧。
Go ahead, check it out.
这是一个猫头鹰。
It's an owl.
是你和黑木吗?
Is that you and Darkwood?
哇。
Wow.
是的。
Yep.
-对，就是我们。——“Abraca-Duo”?
- Yeah, that's us. - The "Abraca-Duo"?
嘿,别法官。这在当时是一个非常容易记住的名字。
Hey, don't judge. It was a very catchy name at the time.
那么，你们现在为什么讨厌对方呢?
So, why do you hate each other now?
哇。嗯…
Wow. Um...
当我们还是露营者的时候，我们很亲密。
When we were campers, we were close.
我对你下了咒语
♪ I put a spell on you ♪
我很酷…
I was like the cool...
训练营的老巨星
older superstar of the camp
她是我的门生。
and she was kinda my protégée.
因为你是我的
♪ Because you're mine ♪
放学后，我们成了伙伴。
After school, we became partners.
一开始，我们只是做了很多街头魔术。
At first, we just did a lot of street magic.
停止你所做的事情
♪ Stop the things you do ♪
但是消息传开了，很快我们就预订了真正的演出。
But word got around and pretty soon we were booking real gigs.
我不是吹牛，但我们在一起真的很棒。
Not to brag, but we were pretty amazing together.
我知道这有点难以置信，但我们确实曾经是一对。
I know it's kinda hard to believe, but we actually used to be a couple.
很明显。
It's obvious.
我是说，你看得出她对你还有感觉。
I mean, you can tell she still has feelings for you.
-我知道，对吧?-是的。
- I know, right? - Yeah.
就像，忘记它，你知道吗?
It's like, get over it, you know?
不管怎样，我们开始制作越来越大的影院，
Anyway, we started doing bigger and bigger theaters,
想在维加斯有自己的演出
trying to get our own show in Vegas.
然后她背着我走了。
Then she went behind my back.
没带我去见一个大电视制作人。
Took a meeting with a big TV booker without me.
我发现后，我们大吵了一架，然后分手了。
When I found out, we got in this huge fight and we broke up.
她做了电视独唱，一夜成名。
She did the solo TV gig and skyrocketed to fame.
我也开始独奏，但是…
I also started to perform solo, but...
这是粗糙的。
It was rough.
一天晚上，我只为一个人做了一个节目……托尼。
One night I did a show for just one person... Tony.
那天早些时候他修理了我的车。
He worked on my car earlier that day.
你能想象为一个人施魔法吗?
Can you imagine just doing magic for one person?
我能。这就是我施魔法的原因。为我的爸爸。
I can. That's why I did magic. For my dad.
我只会为他表演。
I'd only perform for him.
但现在，他…
But now, he's, um...
——他……-嘿，没事的。
- He... - Hey, it's okay.
我们现在不需要谈这个。
We don't have to talk about that now.
快点，我们离开这里。
Come on, let's get out of here.
——要去哪里吗?-让我出去。
- Going somewhere? - Let me out.
你整个夏天都在练习，在练习前偷偷溜走。
You've been pulling this all summer, sneaking away before practice.
你知道是你自己选择来的吗?
You know you chose to come here?
不是真的。我从来没施过魔法。
Not really. I've never even done magic before.
-我父母刚把我送走。——我很抱歉。
- My parents just sent me away. - I'm sorry.
那真的不公平。
That's really not fair.
好吧，你懂的。放我出去。
Okay, you get it. So let me out.
可以这样做。
Could do that.
但如果你选择把整个夏天看作是一种挑战呢?
But what if you chose to look at this whole summer as a kind of challenge?
就像绑着这张网的蟒蛇一样。
Like that constrictor knot holding this net.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
你被困在这里了，就像你被困在这张网里一样。
Well, you're stuck here at camp, just like you're stuck in this net.
你没有选择任何一种情况，但它们确实发生了。
You didn't choose either situation, but they happened.
所以，你有两个选择。
So, you have two options.
你可以继续不开心，被困住，或者你可以做些什么来改变它。
You can continue being unhappy and stuck, or you can do something about it.
改变你的处境。
Change your situation.
我已经见识过你那件紧身衣的威力了。
I've seen what you can do with that straitjacket.
——哇!——哇!
- Whoa! - Whoa!
哈!
Ha!
美好的一天,露营者。
Good day, campers.
还有5天就要参加高帽比赛了。
Just five days until the Top Hat competition.
但是记住，你们不是在和别人竞争，而是在和你们自己竞争。
But remember, you are not competing with each other, but yourselves.
还有彼此。
And also each other.
如发现有松动的兔子，请向维修人员报告。
Please report any loose bunny sightings to the maintenance staff.
午餐将是兔子。
Lunch will be rabbit.
在开玩笑。火腿沙拉。
Kidding. Ham salad.
-你们在干嘛?-我们在这里等你。
- Um, what are you guys doing? - We're waiting here for you.
我有好消息和坏消息要告诉你。
I've got some great news and some less-than-great news.
我想我知道如何治好你的怯场。
I think I know how to cure your stage fright.
这是惊人的。不太好的消息是什么?
That's amazing. What's the less-great news?
它叫做护身符。这可能会变得一团糟。
It's called the gauntlet. And it may get messy.
给我们看一些心脏手术。
Just show us some cardistry.
你以前也为我做过。你可以再做一次。
You did it for me before. You can do it again.
我想我做不到。
I don't think I can.
不要想，就去做。
Don't think, just do it.
做好一切准备。
And be prepared for anything.
我们走吧。告诉我们。
Let's go. Show us.
就是这样。干得好，西奥。
That's it. Yeah, good job, Theo.
露丝,内森,现在。
Ruth, Nathan, now.
两点之间的距离…
The distance between two points...
等于√X 200。
is the square root of X of 200.
嘿，注意点，好吗?
Hey, focus up, okay?
把其他一切都排除在外。只有你和我。
Block everything else out. It's just you and me.
是的,伟大的工作。现在，卷曲成瀑布。正确的。
Yes, great job. Now, friffle into cascade. Right into it.
贾德,维拉,现在!
Judd, Vera, now!
好的，现在查利尔切成L形。
Okay, now charlier into L cuts.
是的!
Yes!
我知道你能做到。
I knew you could do it.
严重吗?
Seriously?
它在。
It's on.
神奇的战斗!
Magic fight!
我们得到他!
We got him!
——我……-等等，他去哪了?
- My... - Wait, where'd he go?
他就像一个有魔力的忍者。
He's like a magic ninja.
哈哈!
Ha ha!
你以为你把我带到你想要的地方。
You think you got me where you want me.
但也许我把你带到了我想要你的地方。
But maybe I got you right where I want you.
Alaka-zip-it。
Alaka-zip-it.
幸运符?
Lucky Charms?
“他们神奇的美味。”明白了吗?
"They're magically delicious." Get it?
我们得到它。
We get it.
你怎么知道的?
How'd you even know?
因为我是魔法忍者。
Because I am a magic ninja.
我们的衣服都毁了。
Our clothes are ruined.
我想我已经搞定了。
I think I got us covered.
是的，但至少想想。
Yeah, but at least think about it.
只有很短的飞行距离，对吗?好吧,再见。
It's only a short flight away, right? Okay, bye.
嘿，他们终于在雪糕里增加了非乳制品的选择。
Hey, they finally added a nondairy option to the ice cream bar.
看，这是一颗破碎的心。
Look, it's one of the broken Hearts.
你要去哪儿?
Where do you think you're going?
我只是想做个不吃冰淇淋的梦。
I was just gonna get some No Cream Ice Dream.
你真的尝不出有什么不同。
You really can't taste the difference.
我不知道。看起来你在骗受害人。
I don't know. It looks like you're trying to trick the Vic.
-骗受害人。维克技巧。-不，我不是。
- Trick the Vic. Trick the Vic. - No, I'm not.
你称自己为“受害者”会有点尴尬。
And it's a bit awkward that you refer to yourself as "the Vic."
选择一个卡。
Pick a card.
嗯，我宁愿不要。
Um, I'd rather not.
选择……一个……卡。
Pick... a... card.
”凯。
'Kay.
好的,记住它。
Okay, memorize it.
现在，我将按最好到最坏的顺序发4张a。
Now, I'm going to deal out the four aces in order from best to worst.
钻石,黑桃,梅花,
Diamonds, spades, clubs,
最后也是最不重要的是心。
and, last but also least, hearts.
别忘了你的卡，好吗?
Don't forget your card, okay?
我会慢慢来，因为我知道你的心，有点慢。
I'll do this slow 'cause I know you Hearts are, a bit slow.
和…繁荣!
And... boom!
你的卡没了。但是，等等，它去哪了?
Your card is gone. But, wait, where'd it go?
这是反问句吗，还是我该回答?
Is that a rhetorical question, or am I supposed to answer it?
打勾，笨蛋。
Check the box, dummy.
哇!
Whoa!
我是怎么做到的?
So, how'd I do it?
我不知道。我什么也没得到。
I don't know. I-I got nothing.
什么都没有。
Nothing.
这就是你和其他的心…什么都没有。
That's all you and the rest of the Hearts are... nothing.
维克技巧。维克技巧。
Trick the Vic. Trick the Vic.
-骗受害人。维克技巧。——嘿,维克。
- Trick the Vic. Trick the Vic. - Hey, Vic.
我知道你是怎么做的。
I know how you do it.
-我抓住你了，伙计。——好的。
- I got you, buddy. - Okay.
如果你知道我是怎么做的，那你就做吧。
If you know how I do it, then you do it.
首先，漂亮的牌力要给你复制。
First off, nice card force to your duplicate.
但我不能精确地模拟你是怎么做到的
But I can't do the trick exactly how you did it
因为……我没有双面胶带。
'cause... I don't have double-stick tape.
好了。
Nice.
剧透!
Spoiler alert!
继续工作。
Carry on.
现在，如果我要这么做，
Now, if I was gonna do it,
我会拿走一张a，红桃a，
I would've taken one of the aces, the ace of hearts,
我就会把它变成你的名片
and I would've turned it into your card.
否则我就会做一个视觉消失。
Or I would've done a visual vanish.
是这样的。
Something like this.
-你教他这个?-我可能帮了一点忙。
- You teach him that? - I may have helped out a little bit.
不错,西奥。
Nice, Theo.
如果我要用一个副本，
And if I was gonna use a duplicate,
我不会让它像纸牌盒那样明显地出现在某个地方。
I wouldn't make it appear somewhere obvious like a card box.
我会让它看起来不可能
I would make it appear somewhere really impossible
比如你裤子的左边口袋。
like your left pants pocket.
什么?不可能。
What? No way.
哇!
Whoa!
但那需要一些你没有的东西…
But that would've required something you don't have...
一个朋友。
A friend.
生病的燃烧。
Sick burn.
西奥!西奥!西奥!
Theo! Theo! Theo!
嘿，你在干什么?给那些回来。
Hey, what are you doing? Give those back.
冷静下来,芽。
Chill out, bud.
这是令人印象深刻。
That was impressive.
那么，让我再展示一个技巧。
So, let me show you one more trick.
也许你能告诉我怎么做这个。
Maybe you can tell me how I do this one.
哇!
Whoa!
——哦。——没有。
- Aw. - No.
不,我的卡片!你怎么能对我的牌这么做!
No, my cards! How could you do this to my cards!
——加油!-你为什么要这么做?
- Come on! - Why would you do that?
-把他们带回来!不!不!-不酷，维克。
- Bring 'em back! No! No! - Not cool, Vic.
你们都有麻烦了。大家都回到铺位上。
You're all in trouble. Everybody, back to the bunk.
我在床上有一副多余的纸牌。
I've got an extra deck of cards in the bunk.
上面有我的《我的世界》里的头像，
You know, they have photos of my Minecraft avatars on them,
但如果你想要，它们是你的。
but they're yours if you want 'em.
谢谢,但是……
Thanks, but...
那些卡片很特别。
those cards were special.
为什么?
Why?
我爸爸给我的。
My dad gave 'em to me.
他是第一个向我展示魔术的人。
He was the first person to ever show me magic.
我的爸爸,他……他是……
My dad, he... He was...
他……他是……他是伟大的。
He... He was... He was great.
他……他就死了。
He... He died.
和I-I-I……
And I-I-I just...
我真的，真的很想他。
I really, really miss him.
你知道，每个人都希望我成为这个伟大的魔术师。
You know, everyone expects me to be this great magician.
但我不是。
But I'm not.
我想我也不想。
And I don't think I really wanna be.
但我不敢告诉我爸爸。
But I'm afraid to tell my dad that.
我说我已知有109种过敏症，
I say I have 109 known allergies,
但是…实际上只有108。
but... it's really only 108.
我不是真的对谷蛋白过敏。
I'm not actually allergic to gluten.
我就是受不了我妈做的俄式牛柳。
I just can't stand my mom's beef stroganoff.
露丝，你有什么想说的吗?
Ruth, is there anything you wanna share?
我以前觉得自己很可爱，像兔子一样。
I used to think I was adorable, like a bunny.
但现在我像鹰一样嗜血。
But now I have this thirst for blood, like a hawk.
你正在向食物链的上游前进。
You're making your way up the food chain.
为你骄傲。
Proud of you.
哇。维拉，我刚才听到你恭维我了吗?
Whoa. Vera, was that a compliment I just heard?
我的意思是，我对你的厌恶一天比一天少了。
What I meant was, every day, I dislike you a little less.
我不会在世界各地进行私人演出。
I don't perform private shows all over the world.
实际上,或任何地方。
Or anywhere, actually.
是啊，我们也算出来了。
Yeah, we kinda figured that.
当我在你们这个年纪的时候，我表演是因为这是世界上最有趣的事情。
When I was your age, I performed because it was the most fun in the world.
我的意思是，这就是我想要的，有我自己的节目，成为那个男人。
I mean, that's all I wanted, to have my own show and be the guy.
然后发生了一件事……
And then something happened...
黑伍德结束了你的伙伴关系。
Darkwood ended your partnership.
-伤透你的心。-让你失去了魔力
- Broke your heart. - Made you lose your mojo.
什么?不。我不会…我不会…嗯…
What? No. I wouldn't... I wouldn't... Um...
不。这不是……
No. That's not...
重点是，伙计们，在那之后，
Well, the point is, guys, is that after that,
我不再在舞台上玩了。
I stopped having fun on stage.
观众看我的时候也不再开心了。
And the audience stopped having fun watching me.
现在我开出租车。
And now I drive a taxi.
男人。连优步都没有?
Man. Not even an Uber?
我的车不够好。它没有资格。
My car's not nice enough. It didn't qualify.
你刚才提到的那个可爱的挑战者呢?
What about that sweet Challenger you came in?
那是租来的。
That is a rental.
好吧。
Okay.
-是的。——好的。
- Yeah. - Okay.
我不得不向爸爸借钱才能租到它。是的。
I had to borrow money from my dad in order to rent it. Yeah.
嗯…
Um...
这不是金魔杖，但是个开始。
It's not a Golden Wand, but it's a start.
谢谢,西奥。
Thanks, Theo.
下一个技巧，
And for my next trick,
我给大家下了个咒语，让大家不再伤心
I put a spell on all of us to quit being sad
祝你度过最美好的夜晚。
and have the best night ever.
-谢谢，谢谢。-嘿，Theo, Janelle在看你呢。
- Thank you, thank you. - Hey, Theo, Janelle's looking at you.
真的吗?
Really?
你觉得是关于什么的?你觉得她的棉花糖用完了?
What do you think it's about? You think she ran out of marshmallows?
她可能把棉花糖用完了。詹妮尔，我们有棉花糖!
She probably ran out of marshmallows. Hey, Janelle, we have marshmallows!
-冷静，冷静!——为什么?
- Chill out, chill out! - Why?
女士们会喜欢你的。
Ooh, lady's gonna like you.
——K-I-S-S-I-N-G。——西奥!
- K-I-S-S-I-N-G. - Theo!
西奥喜欢詹妮尔。西奥喜欢詹妮尔。
Theo likes Janelle. Theo likes Janelle.
你打算什么时候把你是专业魔术师的事实说出来?
When were you gonna come clean about the fact that you're a professional magician?
我不是。
I'm not.
-我看见你和维克在一起这是疯狂的。——谢谢。
- I saw you with Vic. That was crazy. - Thanks.
是啊，你可能在这神奇的事情上发现了一些东西。
Yeah, you might be onto something with this whole magic thing.
很有趣,对吧?
It's fun, right?
这是有趣的。
This is fun.
每个人都冻结。
Everyone freeze.
露丝，你在做什么?
Ruth, what are you doing?
待回来。
Stay back.
我整个夏天都在为这一刻而训练。
I've been training for this moment all summer.
伙计们，我想那是弗雷德。它一定是从笼子里跑出来的。
Guys, I think that's Fred. He must've gotten out of his cage.
感谢上帝。弗雷德的臭腺被切除了。
Thank God. Fred had his stink glands removed.
但我们还是要带他回去。
But we still need to guide him back.
不要听他们的。
Don't listen to them.
不要看他们。
Don't look at them.
只有你和我。
It's just you and me.
这些看起来不像弗雷德的条纹。
Those don't look like Fred's stripes.
不。我mustelid过敏。
No. My mustelid allergy.
内森,持有它。这不是弗雷德。这不是弗雷德!
Nathan, hold it. It's not Fred. It's not Fred!
我这么做是出于爱。
I'm doing this out of love.
别担心。我有一个给你!
Don't worry. I got one for you!
Sker-ploosh !
Sker-ploosh!
不!别碰我。
No! Don't touch me.
明确的。
Clear.
嘘。
Shh.
早上好,露营者。
Good morning, campers.
还有两天就要戴大礼帽了
Two days until Top Hat,
我很兴奋，我今天可以吃午饭了，
and I am so excited I may actually eat our lunch today,
那将是肉糕，也将是晚餐。
which will be meat loaf, as will be dinner.
事实上，这个夏天剩下的时间，我们只需要和肉卷一起吃。
In fact, we're just gonna roll with meat loaf for the rest of the summer.
安迪,救命!
Andy, help!
他们也抓住了我。
They got me too.
的帮助!
Help!
嘿，怎么回事?把这些带回来。
Hey, what's going on? Bring those back.
穿过。
Coming through.
他们为最后的演出检查了一切。
They've checked everything out for the final performance.
你对老鹰伊森做了什么?伊桑·霍克是我的全部。
What are you doing with Ethan the hawk? Ethan Hawk is my whole act.
你不睡，你就输了，小家伙。
You snooze, you lose, little one.
一切都在哪儿?他们弄乱了我的东西。
Where's everything? They're messing with my things.
那么,什么是…我的表。
So, what is... My table.
没有什么。没有球，没有牌。
There's nothing. There's no balls, no cards.
-钻石队检查了所有的道具。——什么?
- The Diamonds checked out all the props. - What?
-真不敢相信。——什么?
- I don't believe this. - What?
-他们使我们的心变小了。-怎么会这样?
- They shrunk our hearts. - How'd that happen?
他们把烘干机的设置调到了“重型”。
They switched the dryer setting to "heavy duty."
混合运动服装不是“重型”。
Polyblend athletic wear is not "heavy duty."
你觉得你是不是放错位置了?
Do you think maybe you just put it on the wrong setting?
你是…你是在指责我洗衣服的错误吗?
Are you... Are you accusing me of making a laundry mistake?
我洗衣服从不出错，先生。我创造了洗衣奇迹。
I do not make laundry mistakes, sir. I make laundry miracles.
钻石毁了我们的行为。
The Diamonds have ruined our act.
我们还有计数轮。
We still have the counting wheel.
他们毁了一切!
They ruined everything!
关于黑木镇的事你是对的。她是冷血动物。
You were right about Darkwood. She is cold-blooded.
我们不可能为最后的演出及时准备好新材料。
We'll never get new stuff together in time for the final performance.
面对现实吧，伙计们，都结束了。他们击败了我们。
Face it, guys, it's over. They beat us.
反正我们也没有真正的机会。
It's not like we ever really had a chance anyway.
那不是真的。还记得你们刚来的时候有多可怕吗?
That's not true. Remember how horrible you guys were when you first got here?
你们现在少多了。
You guys suck way less now.
-多谢了-你是在恭维我吗?
- Thanks a lot. - Was that supposed to be a compliment?
说真的，我们不能放弃。
Seriously, we can't quit.
因为当事情变得困难时，心脏就会跳动起来。
'Cause when the going gets hard, the Hearts get going.
那很好。你刚想出来的?
That was pretty good. You just came up with that?
-很好，不是吗?-是的。这是可怕的。
- That was good, wasn't it? - Yeah. That was awesome.
你知道吗?我想我知道我们需要什么了。
You know what? I think I know what we need.
跟我来。
Follow me.
好的,帮派。
Okay, gang.
我们到了。
And here we are.
好吧。
Okay.
哇!
Whoa!
你是怎么做到的?磁铁或电线吗?
How'd you do that? Magnets or wires?
既不。现代科技。
Neither. Just modern technology.
那么，我们在这里做什么?
So, what are we doing here?
一天晚上，我在堪萨斯城演出，
One night, I was playing a show in Kansas City,
航空公司把我的机箱放错飞机了。
and the airline put my prop case on the wrong plane.
哦,不太好。
Ooh, not good.
我只好在机场的便利店里随便找些东西凑合着用。
I had to improvise with whatever I could find at the airport convenience store.
而这正是我现在要求你们做的。
And that is exactly what I'm challenging you guys to do right now.
谁说我们需要道具?
Who says we need props?
戏法是魔术师创造的，而不是魔术师创造的。
Magicians create the trick, not the other way around.
你可以把它想象成一个神奇的寻宝活动。
Think of it as like a magical treasure hunt.
通常在寻宝游戏中，参与者会被提供
Um, typically in a treasure hunt, the participants are provided
有线索，有地图，有传说…
with clues, a map, or a legend...
——走吧。30分钟后见。-我们会得到线索还是地图?
- Let's go. See you in 30 minutes. - Are we gonna get clues or a map?
玩得开心。想想看，好吗?即兴发挥。
Have fun. Figure it out, all right? Improvise.
也许这一个。
Maybe this one.
这是垃圾。这不是形状。
This is garbage. This is just not the shape.
那
That.
内森,内森。
Nathan, Nathan.
对不起,每一个人。我能引起你的注意吗?
Excuse me, everybody. Can I get your attention?
今天，我们将向你展示一些魔术。
Today, we're gonna show you some magic.
把它拿走，维拉。
Take it away, Vera.
太酷了。
So cool.
——明白了吗?-是的。
- Got it? - Yeah.
酷。
Cool.
对不起，这个刻度有多精确?
Excuse me, how accurate is that scale?
测量重量到千分之一磅。
Measures weight down to a thousandth of a pound.
如果他能猜出确切的重量，我们能免费得到这个糖果吗?
If he can guess the exact weight, can we have this candy for free?
确定。这是不可能的。
Sure. That's impossible.
这是不可能的，还是2.173磅?
Is it impossible, or is it 2.173 pounds?
2.173磅。
2.173 pounds.
——是的!——这是不可思议的。
- Yeah! - That's incredible.
酷,伙计。我们省了11.54美元(含税)。
Cool, dude. We just saved $11.54, tax included.
哇!
Whoo!
我正试着学习如何正确持球。
I'm trying to learn to hold the ball right.
这些神奇的孩子们怎么了?
What's up with all these weird magic kids?
群lame-os。
Bunch of lame-os.
嘿!你说的那些是我的朋友。
Hey! Those are my friends you're talking about.
怪异让我们很棒。
And weird is what makes us awesome.
攻击!抓住他们的眼睛。
Attack! Go for their eyes.
走,走!
Go, go!
我还会碰一只兔子吗?
Am I ever going to touch a bunny?
总有一天，我保证你会的。
One day, I promise you will.
不是只有一打逃跑了吗?现在他们无处不在。
Didn't only a dozen escape? Now they're everywhere.
它们是如何繁殖的?
How are they multiplying?
我会让你父母解释的。
You know, I'm gonna let your parents explain that one.
好吧，已经超过你的宵禁时间了。进去睡觉吧。
Okay, way past your curfew. Get in there and get to bed.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
-我有账要算。-我保证他会来的
- I've got a score to settle. - I promise you he'll show.
用黑木制作嘿,!
Hey, Darkwood!
他现在就在那里。好吧。我待会再打给你。
There he is right now. All right. I'll talk to you later.
把电话挂了，你这个怪物。
Get off the phone, you monster.
你刚才叫我怪物吗?
Did you just call me a monster?
破坏我和我的事业是一回事，但是孩子呢?
It's one thing to sabotage me and my career, but children?
你真的能接受这个退出的事情吗?
Were you really cool with this whole sign-out thing?
严重吗?我已经罚了我的铺位，还让他们把所有的道具都退了。
Seriously? I already punished my bunk and made them return all the props.
但是你怎么了?
But what's up with you?
当我第一次听说你今年夏天要来的时候
You know, when I first heard you were coming this summer,
见到你我很兴奋。
I was excited to see you.
我以为我们之间的争执已经过去了
I thought we'd be past whatever beef we had
我们可以…朋友了。
and we could just be... friends again.
你说得倒容易。
That is so easy for you to say.
当你抛弃我时，我一无所有，而你拥有一切。
I got nothing and you got everything when you dropped me.
我放弃了你?
I dropped you?
-你背叛了我-我从没背叛过你。
- You cheated on me. - I never cheated on you.
你欺骗了我们。
You cheated on our act.
”凯。好吧，我承认。我背着你参加了那个电视会议。
'Kay. Yes, fine, I'll admit it. I took that TV meeting behind your back.
你总是叫我你的门徒。
You were always calling me your protégée.
我想看看我自己能不能做到。
I wanted to see if I could do it on my own.
你的背叛终于被揭露了。
Your treachery is finally revealed.
是的。他们认为我在电视上独自表演会更好。
Yes. They thought I would be a better solo act on TV.
他们讨厌Abraca-Duo这个名字。
And they hated the name Abraca-Duo.
当时它很吸引人!
It was catchy at the time!
-但我拒绝了——到底!
- But I told them no. - Exactly!
什么?
What?
我告诉他们我不是一个独角戏演员。
I told them I wasn't a solo act.
我想为我们俩谈点条件
I was trying to negotiate a deal for the both of us,
但我还没来得及解释你就辞职了。
but you quit before I could explain.
——为什么……你为什么不阻止我?-因为你发疯了。
- Why... Why didn't you stop me? - 'Cause you were flipping out.
你不回我的电话和短信。
You wouldn't return any of my phone calls or texts.
你忙着在任何一个愿意听的魔术师面前说我的坏话。
You were too busy bad-mouthing me to any magician that would listen.
所以我一个人做了这件事。
So I did the act alone.
没有你，我很害怕。
I was terrified to do it without you.
-太疯狂了。——为什么?
- That is crazy. - Why?
你知道那个电视布克一开始为什么选你吗?
You know why that TV booker picked you in the first place?
因为，我是说，看看你。
Because, I mean, look at you.
你注定要成为一个明星。
You were destined to be a star.
我知道，他知道，每个人都知道。
I knew it, he knew it, everyone knew it.
和…显然，我注定要开一辆出租马车。
And... evidently I was destined to drive a cab.
男人。连优步都没有?
Man. Not even an Uber?
我在这里倾吐我的心声。
I am pouring my heart out here.
我很抱歉。我很抱歉。
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
安迪，你是我见过的最好的魔术师之一。
Andy, you are one of the best magicians I have ever seen.
是的，这是真的。
Yes, that is true.
我所知道的几乎都是从你和普雷斯顿那里学来的。
I learned almost everything I know from you and Preston.
看着你这个夏天在床上工作
And watching you work with your bunk this summer
提醒我你有多棒。
reminded me how awesome you are.
不客气
You're welcome.
别傻了，否则我不会告诉你电话上是谁。
Stop being a jerk, or I am not going to tell you who I was on the phone with.
为什么?你在和谁通电话?
Why? Who were you on the phone with?
我朋友经营着金银岛
Well, my friend runs Treasure Island,
明天的日场演出在最后一刻被取消了
and he just had a last-minute cancellation for a matinee performance tomorrow
他问我是否知道有谁准备好进入这个阶段了。
and asked me if I knew anybody who was ready to work that stage.
是我推荐你的。
And I recommended you.
我不知道该怎么办…日场吗?真的吗?连夜场都没有?
I don't know what to... A matinee? Really? Not even an evening show?
严重吗?你到底要不要那个演出?
Seriously? Do you want the gig or not?
-嗨。——不要说话。
- Hey. - Don't speak.
什么也别说。
Don't say a word.
等一等。
Hold on.
他们邀请你去金银岛看演出。
They've offered you a show at Treasure Island.
-黑木已经发短信给你了?-大约一小时前。
- Darkwood texted you already? - About an hour ago.
祝贺你。这是……这是巨大的。
Congratulations. That is... It's huge.
我知道,对吧?
I know, right?
你看起来不太高兴。
You don't seem very happy.
如果我参加演出，我会及时回来看演出的，
Well, if I take the gig, I'll be back in time for the show,
但我明天不会在这里帮他们一起行动，
but I won't be here tomorrow to help the bunk put their acts together,
和…相信我，那些混蛋，他们需要我。
and... I mean, trust me, those screw-ups, they need me.
你需要什么?
What do you need?
你这辈子都在梦想这一刻，不是吗?
You've been dreaming about this moment your whole life, haven't you?
我想是的。
I think so.
我不能告诉你该做什么，但我内心深处知道，
I can't tell you what to do, but I know that deep down,
你已经有了答案。
you already have the answer.
那床铺呢?我不能不说再见就走。
What about the bunk? I can't leave without saying goodbye.
让他们睡觉，好吗?走了。我明天早上再跟他们解释。
Let 'em sleep, all right? Go. I'll explain to them in the morning.
——走吧。——好的。
- Go. - Okay.
早上好,露营者。
Good morning, campers.
今天是我们一直在等待的一天。
Today is the day we've all been waiting for.
今天你们的父母将看到你们这个暑假所做的一切。
Today your parents will see all that you've worked on this summer.
午餐是热辣龙虾配牛肝菌和法式鲜奶油烩饭。
Lunch will be lobster thermidor with a porcini and crème fraîche risotto.
请随意向你的父母提及今天的晚餐。
Feel free to mention today's meal to your parents.
看起来他昨晚根本就没睡过这里。
It doesn't look like he even slept here last night.
-是啊，他的垃圾袋也没了。-他好像消失了。
- Yeah, and his trash bags are gone. - It's like he vanished.
我出现了。
And I have appeared.
好了，临时会议，五分钟。来吧。
All right, bunk meeting, five minutes. Come on.
穿好衣服。我们走吧。
Get dressed. Let's go.
——什么?严重吗?——请问?
- What? Seriously? - Excuse me?
-他去维加斯了?是的，他去了维加斯。
- He went to Vegas? - Yes, he went to Vegas.
他得到了表演的机会。这就是魔术师所做的。
He's been given the chance to perform. That's what magicians do.
这就是你今晚要做的。
That's what you're gonna be doing tonight.
他会及时回来看你比赛的。
And he will be back in time to watch you compete.
我们该如何竞争?我是说，没有他我们做不到。
How are we supposed to compete? I mean, we can't do it without him.
他会帮我们一起行动。
He was gonna help us put our acts together.
——正确的。-但现在我来了。
- Right. - But now I'm here.
我将帮助你们一起行动。好吧?
And I will help you put your act together. All right?
所以，让我们卷起袖子
So, let's just roll up our sleeves
然后开始工作。
and get to work.
不要碰萨米。他今天早上有点不舒服。
Don't touch Sammy. He was a little bitey this morning.
我们开始吧。这是她要选的卡片。
Here we go. This is the card that she will choose.
她会选这张牌。这是一个保证。
She's gonna pick this card. It's a guarantee.
你看到了吗?”凯。
You see that? 'Kay.
现在，我要把它藏起来妥善保管。
Now, I'm gonna tuck it away for safekeeping.
把它放在那儿。
Put it right there.
现在我要用一副完全不同的牌。
Now I'm gonna take a completely different deck of cards, right here.
她可以选择这些牌中的任何一张。
And she can choose any one of these cards.
绝对的。
Absolutely.
点击其中一个的背面，好吗?
Go ahead and just touch the back of one, okay?
我们笑是因为她有这么多选择吗?
Are we laughing because she has so many choices?
这就是我们笑的原因吗?
Is that what we're laughing about?
——这一个。——卡。你确定吗?
- This one. - That card. Are you sure?
这就是那张牌。“凯?
So, this is the card. 'Kay?
我偷偷怀疑我们不会忘记这件事的，好吗?
And I have a sneaking suspicion we're not gonna forget this one, okay?
这是你的名片。现在，继续，把它放在你的胸部。
Here's your card. Now, go ahead and place it towards your chest.
就在那里，就在你的心上。不要看。
Right there, right on your heart. Don't look.
好吧，现在来点俏皮话。
All right, now take a little peeksy.
告诉观众，这是红牌还是黑牌?
Tell the audience, is it a red card or a black card?
它是红色的。
It's red.
对，不是卡片背面。
Yeah, not the back of the card.
我们说的是牌面。实际的卡片。
We're talking about the face of the card. The actual card.
是什么颜色的?
What color's that?
它是红色的。
It's red.
我能看一下吗?
Can I see that?
噢!
Ooh!
是的，那是红方块5。
Yes, that is a red five of diamonds.
和…这真的很尴尬
And... this is really awkward
给那些认为我搞砸了的人。
for anyone in here who thought I messed up.
大家为海莉鼓掌吧哈利!
Give it up for Haley, everybody. Haley!
谢谢你！
Thank you.
黑木说得对。她说你会是一个很好的日场魔术师。
Darkwood was right about you. She said you'd be a good matinee magician.
她说的?这实际上有点侮辱人。
She said that? That is actually a little insulting.
但你在黄金时间会更好。
But that you'd be even better in prime time.
今晚来个表演怎么样?
How'd you like a showcase tonight?
今晚吗?Tonight-tonight吗?
Tonight? Tonight-tonight?
事实上，今晚有点复杂。
Actually, tonight is a little complicated.
让我简单地告诉你。
Let me make this simple for you.
这里有上百万的魔术师，他们都想看8点的表演，
There's a million magicians who would kill for an eight o'clock show on the strip,
我给你一个机会。
and I'm offering you one.
你今晚表现得很好，这个剧院可能会成为你很长一段时间的家。
You do well tonight, this theater could be your home for a very long time.
你说呢?
What do you say?
让我们做它。是的。
Let's do it. Yes.
太好了。把东西打开，就像在自己家一样。
Excellent. Unpack your things, make yourself at home.
太好了。
Great.
我有一只蚕，她不仅会丝，还会木!
I have a silkworm that not only makes silk, she also makes wood!
哇!
Whoa!
他的名字叫科尔内留斯·凯斯勒。这是我的名片。
The name is Kornelius Kessler. Here's my card.
如果你喜欢你看到的，请在Yelp上评论我。
If you liked what you saw, review me on Yelp.
我儿子今天表演。
My son is performing today.
当你看到丝绒领结时，你就知道你得到了一个高质量的表演。
When you see the velvet bow tie, you know you're getting a quality act.
-领结怎么样?-我就在这里。
- What about the bow tie? - I've got it right here.
很高兴见到你。
It's so nice to meet you.
原谅我。嗨。这张有人拍了吗?谢谢。
Excuse me. Hi. Is this one taken? Thanks.
好了，红心们，振作起来。嘿，伙计们，过来。
Okay, Hearts, gather up. Hey, guys, come here.
好吧，我们得好好谈谈。
All right, um, we have to have a little heart-to-Hearts.
-怎么回事?-安迪打电话来了
- What's going on? - Well, Andy called
不幸的是,
and, unfortunately,
他毕竟不能及时赶回来戴大礼帽了。
he is not going to be able to make it back in time for the Top Hat after all.
但他想让我告诉你他有多骄傲
But he wanted me to tell you how very, very proud he is
你们每一个人。
of each and every one of you.
当然，我也是。
And, of course, so am I.
我们该怎么办?
What are we supposed to do?
当事情变得困难时，心脏就会跳动起来。
When the going gets hard, the Hearts get going.
我们来做这件事。
Let's do this thing.
我们来做这件事。这就是精神。
Let's do this thing. That's the spirit.
西奥,安迪特别……
Theo, Andy specifically...
嗯,哪里来的……他去了?
Well, where'd... he go?
普雷斯顿。
Preston, you're on.
好吧。的地方,好吗?祝你好运。
Okay. Places, all right? Good luck.
从一开始，我们就对这种壮举感到惊叹
Since the dawn of time, we have marveled at the feats
由少数敢于窥见天外的人来完成。
performed by the select few who dare peer into the beyond.
魔术师。
Magicians.
欢迎,欢迎。
Welcome, welcome.
现在，这个夏天，你们的每一个孩子
Now, this summer, every single one of your children
已经在这个神秘的秩序中赢得了一席之地。
have earned their place in this mystical order.
但他们当中谁学得最多?
But who among them has learned the most?
那么，谁注定会拿着礼帽和金魔杖呢?
And which ones are destined to hold the Top Hat and the Golden Wand?
好吧。做好被震惊和震惊的准备，
All right. Be prepared to be shocked and astounded,
因为今年的比赛从现在开始。
because this year's competition begins now.
首先，代表红心小屋的露丝·布鲁塞尔巴赫。
First up, representing the Hearts cabin, Ruth Brusselbach.
-摸摸小兔!-你能行的，露丝!
- Touch the bunny! - You can do it, Ruth!
你能做到的。来吧。兔子的爱是真实的!你是一个武士。
You can do it. Come on. Bunny love is real! You're a samurai.
接下来是代表钻石小屋的维克·德·安东尼奥。
Next up, representing the Diamond cabin, Vic d'Antonio.
我是受害者，我提前向你们所有的父母道歉
Hey, I'm the Vic, and I apologize to all you parents in advance
因为我又要赢得金魔杖了。
'cause I'm about to win the Golden Wand, again.
现在选一张牌，任意一张。只是碰它。
Now pick a card, any card. Just touch it.
好吧。
Okay.
记住它。不要忘记它。
Memorize it. Don't forget it.
我会把甲板交给我的助手。
I'll hand the deck to my assistant.
她的工作很简单。现在看这个。
Her job's easy. Now watch this.
这是你的名片吗?
Was this your card?
你怎么知道我在这里?
How'd you know I was in here?
你知道现在有个魔术表演吗?
You know there's a magic show going on right now?
如果安迪不在，我就不表演。
I'm not performing if Andy's not here.
你的家人在外面。和你的妈妈。
Your family's out there. And your mom.
你不想让你妈妈看到你这个暑假学到的所有魔法吗?
Don't you want your mom to see all the magic you've learned this summer?
她不在乎魔法。她甚至不知道这个地方。
She doesn't care about magic. She didn't even know about this place.
她以为那是魔法营。你能相信吗?
She thought it was called Magic Camp. Can you believe that?
嗯,有点。
Um, sort of.
魔术是我和爸爸的最爱。
Magic was my thing with my dad.
我来是因为他替我申请的。
I'm here because he applied for me.
和…现在他走了。那么，重点是什么呢?
And... now he's gone. So, what's the point?
你这么说很有意思。
Interesting you should say that.
红心杯的下一位，薇拉·科斯塔。
Next up from the Hearts, Vera Costa.
我把所有的申请都存档了。
I keep all my applications on file.
和…我当然记得你的。
And... I remember yours, of course.
等一等。
Hold on.
因为那是我。我是红心j。
'Cause that's me. I'm the jack of hearts.
这就是你。你是红心之王。
And that's you. You're the king of hearts.
等等，谁开的枪?
Wait, who shot this?
这是难以置信的。你是不可思议的,西奥。
That's incredible. You're incredible, Theo.
哇。你看到这个把戏了吗?
Wow. Did you just see that trick?
我儿子是个了不起的魔术师。
My son is an amazing magician.
我不知道他是怎么做到的。
I don't know how he does any of it.
但你可能看不到的是，他已经克服了多少困难。
But what you might not see is how much he has overcome.
多少……
How much...
我希望西奥能看到我在他身上看到的一切。
I wish Theo could see everything that I see in him.
但他把一切都锁在心里
But he keeps it all locked inside,
魔法是开启他的第一步。
and magic is the first thing that's unlocked him.
我想这是一种技巧，对吧?
I guess that's sort of a trick, right?
这就是为什么你不带他去你的魔法训练营
That's why you'd be crazy not to take him for your magic camp,
或者研究所，或者别的什么。
or institute, or whatever.
我可能有点古怪
Well, I may be eccentric,
但是，我从来没有像现在这样被申请说服过。
but, I don't think I've ever been more persuaded by an application.
西奥，我不能告诉你该怎么做
Theo, I cannot tell you what to do,
但我知道在内心深处你已经有了答案。
but I know deep down you already have the answer.
但我不能一个人上去。
But I can't go up there alone.
安迪说你会这么说的。
Andy said you would say that.
但他让我告诉你，如果你在舞台上迷路了，
But he told me to tell you that if you lose your way on stage,
只要看看翅膀就行了
just look to the wings
你会找到一个真正的魔术师来帮助你。
and you'll find a true magician to help you.
这是什么意思?
What does that mean?
只有一个办法可以知道。
Only one way to find out.
好吧，我需要一点帮助。
Okay, I'll need a little help here.
年轻的绅士，你在学校的储物柜号码是多少?
Young gent, what is your locker combination at school?
别担心，我不会偷你的作业，也不会替你做。
Don't worry, I'm not gonna steal your homework, or do it for you.
16岁,98年,17岁。
Sixteen, 98, 17.
太好了,好了。
Great, okay.
女士，输入1-6-9-8-1-7。
Ma'am, type in 1-6-9-8-1-7.
然后点击时间。
And then hit times.
好吧，先生，你的生日是什么?你。
Okay, um, you, sir, what is your birthday? You.
10月9日。
October 9.
10月9日吗?- 9,很好。
October 9? 10-9, great.
女士，输入1-0-9。然后打次。
Ma'am, type in 1-0-9. Then hit times.
不要大声说出来，输入你初吻时的年龄。
Don't say this out loud, but type in the age you were when you had your first kiss.
现在，点击等于，一次念一个数给我听。
Now, hit equals and read the number aloud to me one digit at a time.
- 7。- 7。
- Seven. - Seven.
- 4。- 4。
- Four. - Four.
——零。——零。
- Zero. - Zero.
- 4。- 4。
- Four. - Four.
——零,两个。——两个。
- Zero, two. - Two.
一,二。
One, two.
对不起，我写得乱七八糟。
Sorry for my messy handwriting.
所以,74040212。
So, 74,040,212.
我不可能知道这些信息
Okay, so there's no possible way I could've known any of the information
你今晚要给我的
that you were gonna give me tonight.
然而，我们用你们的数字创造了这个巨大的数字。
Yet, we used your numbers to create this huge number.
现在，我想请大家注意这个神秘的信封。
Now, I would like to call your attention to this envelope of mystery.
今天早些时候，我把我的预测放进了这个信封里。
Earlier today, I put my prediction inside this envelope.
现在我来告诉你们。
And now I am going to reveal it to you.
大象。惊人的,对吧?
Elephant. Amazing, right?
我知道你很困惑。这是上下颠倒的。
I see you're confused. It's upside down.
- Ho !——“大象”。
- Ho! - "Elephant."
我的…
My...
我是一个mathemagician。
I'm a mathemagician.
最后是为钻石乐队表演的詹妮尔·桑托斯。
And finally, performing for the Diamonds, Janelle Santos.
詹妮尔。
Janelle.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
一个,两个……
One, two...
三。
Three.
——我……哇。——哇!
- My... Wow. - Whoo!
这是最好的一年。
This is the best year yet.
好了，当评委们在整理结果的时候，
All right, while the judges are tabulating the results,
我想唱首歌感谢你。
I would like to say thank you by singing a song.
嗯…
Um...
原谅我。
Excuse me.
好吧。最后，最后一场表演，请允许我介绍提奥·摩西。
Okay. For our final, final performance, may I present Theo Moses.
——哇!——哇!
- Whoo! - Whoo!
你们的人数比我预料的要多得多。
There are a lot more of you than I expected.
你知道吗?让我……
You know what? Let me just...
魔法就是感知……
Magic is all about perception...
你所看到的和实际发生的。
What you're seeing versus what's really happening.
就像现在。
Like right now.
你看不见我手里的一副牌，
You don't see a deck of cards in my hands,
但是…现在你做的事情。
but... now you do.
我需要一个助手来玩这个把戏。
I'm going to need an assistant for this trick.
妈妈，你能上来帮我一下吗?
Mom, can you please come up here and help me out?
哇。他真的拥有它了。
Wow. He's really owning it out there.
你知道他会的。
As you knew he would.
你能把这些都看一遍确保它们都是不同的吗?
Can you just look through these just to make sure they're all different?
别人看见我了吗?
Have the others seen me?
-我看不错。-不，不，他们不知道你在这里。
- Looks good to me. - No, no, they have no idea you're here.
一副牌有五十二张，
Fifty-two cards in the deck,
但每一个都有不同的故事。
but each one has a different story to tell.
我知道他们自己能做到。现在他们也知道了。
I knew they could do it on their own. Now they know it too.
你把一切都计划得很完美。
You planned everything perfectly.
不，我觉得你有。
No, I think you did.
我吗?
Me?
小丑有点像个未知数，就像我的弟弟卡梅隆一样。
The joker is a bit of a wild card, just like my little brother, Cameron.
他有时会惹恼我，但没有他我会不知所措。
He annoys me sometimes, but I'd be lost without him.
事实上，卡梅隆，你过来一下。
In fact, Cameron, why don't you come over here.
在从维加斯回来的路上，我把它拼在了一起。
On the drive back from Vegas, I put it together.
整个夏天，新手铺，黑木，西奥。
This whole summer, the newbie bunk, Darkwood, Theo.
如果你想看得更清楚，可以靠近一点。
Feel free to come closer if you want a better look.
这是一个很长的技巧来帮助我恢复我的生活。
It's one long trick to help me get my life together.
你知道他们怎么说的。
Well, you know what they say.
你不相信的把戏才是最好的把戏。
The trick you don't believe is a trick is the best trick of all.
在这个世界上创造更多魔法的方式
The way to create more magic in the world
不是通过创造更多的魔法。
is not by creating more magic.
——没错。-是啊，我还是不明白
- Exactly. - Yeah, I still don't get that one.
你还没让我说完。
You didn't let me finish.
通过创造魔术师。
It's by creating magicians.
这张牌是我，红心j。
This card is me, the jack of hearts.
你真好，老头子。
You are good, old man.
这张卡片是我爸爸…
And this card is my dad...
红心之王。
the king of hearts.
我每天都想着这张卡片。
I think about this card every day.
现在，我妈妈的卡片是红心皇后。
Now, my mom's card is the queen of hearts.
但她在哪里?
But where is she?
我告诉你一个秘密。
I'll tell you a secret.
有时我忘了这张卡片是相信我的。
Sometimes I forgot that this card believed in me.
但即使我没有意识到，
But even when I didn't realize it,
红心女王一直在我身边。
the queen of hearts was always there for me.
红心皇后。我很高兴找到了它。
The queen of hearts. So happy I found it.
在这副牌中，这四张牌最接近我的心。
Out of all the cards in the deck, these four are closest to my heart.
但我妈妈有一些特别的地方。
But there's something extra special about my mom.
她会改变她接触的一切。
She changes everything she touches.
妈妈，你能帮我碰一张卡片吗?
Mom, can you just touch a card for me?
什么?
What?
这是奇怪的。妈，你能不能再摸一个?
That's weird. Um, Mom, can you just touch another?
这是奇怪的。
This is strange.
这副牌中应该只有一个红心皇后。
There's only supposed to be one queen of hearts in the deck.
好吧，妈妈，帮我把手。
Okay, Mom, just hold your hand out for me.
我不知道她是怎么做到的，也不知道为什么我这么久才意识到，
I don't know how she does it, or why it took me this long to realize it,
但是…我妈妈很有魔力。
but... my mother is magic.
哦。
Aw.
是的,是的!什么是竞争。
Yes, yes! What a competition.
美丽。好吧。
Beautiful. All right.
现在，今年高帽比赛的冠军是…
And now, the winner of this year's Top Hat competition is...
非常感谢你的到来。
Thank you so much for coming.
来吧，多一点幽默感。我们开始吧。
Come on, get a sense of humor. Here we go.
好吧。
All right.
今年大礼帽的冠军是…
And the winner for the Top Hat this year...
的心。
the Hearts.
我们赢了!我们赢了!
We won! We won!
——安迪?——这是安迪。
- Andy? - It's Andy.
我真为你们骄傲。我都看到了，伙计。
I'm so proud of you guys. I saw the whole thing, buddy.
——是的!——好的。很好。
- Yes! - Okay. Very good.
现在是…
And now for the...
现在的…
Now for the...
金魔杖的赢家，
The winner of the Golden Wand,
《钻石》，詹妮尔·桑托斯。
from the Diamonds, Janelle Santos.
起床。
Get up here.
走了。鞠躬。
Go. Take a bow.
——什么?-克里斯蒂娜，我成功了!我做到了!
- What? - Kristina, I did it! I did it!
我真为你骄傲。
I am so proud of you.
你在这里做什么?你的大型演出怎么了?
What are you doing here? What happened to your big show?
我跳过它。
I skipped it.
伙计，我看了你的全套装备。
And, dude, I saw your whole set.
什么?我讨厌说这个词，因为我讨厌这个词，
What? I hate to say this phrase because I hate this phrase,
但我的头脑真的被震撼了。
but my mind was literally blown.
等待。你把镜子放在那里。
Wait. You put that mirror there.
你知道，有时候需要别人来帮助你看清自己。
You know, sometimes it takes somebody else to help you see yourself.
哇。你的声音和普雷斯顿一模一样。
Wow. You just sounded exactly like Preston.
-是的，不是吗?-是的。
- I did, didn't I? - Yeah.
好的，我们会解决的。
Okay, we'll work on that.
你能为我鼓掌两次吗?
Can you clap twice for me?
你会跺脚吗?
Can you stomp your feet?
分解它。
Break it down.
哇!
Whoo!
谢谢你！你的铺位太糟糕了。
Thank you. Your bunk killed it.
-非常感谢你做的一切。——再见。
- Thanks so much for everything. - Bye.
嘿。我很抱歉不能参加《金银岛》的演出。
Hey. I am so sorry about ditching the Treasure Island show.
我没给你惹太多麻烦吧?
I didn't get you in too much trouble, did I?
不,它很好。
No, it's fine.
他们实际上邀请你下周末再来。
They actually invited you back next weekend.
——真的吗?——没有。
- Really? - No.
他们终身禁止你。
They banned you for life.
安迪，那真是一场盛大的演出。
Andy, that was a really big gig.
幸运的是，我钓到了一个更大的。
Well, luckily, I landed an even bigger one.
——你做了吗?在哪里?——在这里。
- You did? Where? - Right here.
你现在看到的是新上任的青年人才发展部主任。
You are looking at the new director of youth talent development.
普雷斯顿为我安排了一项全年的儿童童子军活动。
Preston offered me a year-round gig scouting for kids.
——太好了。-这就是我想去的地方。
- That's great. - This is where I wanna be.
最疯狂的是，我在维加斯的舞台上意识到这一点。
And the craziest part is, is I realized that when I was on stage in Vegas.
但是我的朋友说你做得很好。观众喜欢你。
But my friend said that you did great. The audience loved you.
是的。我杀了。
Yeah. I killed.
我要实现我的梦想。
I got to live the dream.
它是令人惊异的。
It was amazing.
但奇怪的是，感觉并没有那么棒
But weird part is, is it didn't feel as amazing
今年夏天帮助孩子们。
as helping the kids this summer.
安迪。
Andy.
你可以留下来和我一起工作。
You know, you could stick around and work here with me.
你们应该知道我在凯撒的标题吧?
You do know I headline at Caesars, right?
是的。我想我听说过。那很酷。那很酷。
Yeah. I think I heard about that. That's cool. That's cool.
但你可以找个时间来帮我。
But you could come feature for me sometime.
这个世界需要一点abraca duo。
The world could use a little Abraca-Duo.
交易。
Deal.
-哇，那真是个糟糕的名字。-是的。
- And, wow, that is a really terrible name. - Yeah.
嗨,爸爸。
Hey, Dad.
贾德。
Judd.
我不明白你的意思。你为什么没有表演?
I don't understand. Why didn't you perform?
不，我表演了。
No, I did perform.
所有红心的戏服，都是我的。
All the Hearts' costumes, those are me.
那些服装是你设计的?甚至是快速变化的惯例?
You designed those costumes? Even the quick-change routine?
他们所有人。
All of them.
我知道你想让我当魔术师
Look, I know you want me to be a magician,
但是…今年夏天，我意识到我不是。
but... this summer I realized I'm not one.
我就是喜欢设计服装。
I just love designing costumes.
我喜欢用时尚给我的朋友们带来神奇的生活。
I love using fashion to bring my friends' magic to life.
那你就错了……
Then you're mistaken...
因为，孩子，这很神奇。
because that, son, is magic.
我想我鼻子里有毛了。我要去灌水。
I think I got fur in my nose. I'm gonna go irrigate.
——嘿!我的天啊。哇。薛西斯,嘿!我会想你的。
- Hey! My gosh. Wow. - Xerxes, hey! I'm gonna miss you.
当心!
Look out!
-你怎么做到的?你得告诉我。-你真的想知道?
- How'd you do that? You have to tell me. - You really wanna know?
-是的。-明年来和我一起野营吧。
- Yeah. - Come to camp with me next year.
-我可以吗，妈妈?——不。
- Can I, Mom? - Nope.
因为明年夏天你要和我一起去露营。瑜伽阵营。
'Cause next summer you're going to camp with me. Yoga camp.
你说什么?
Say what?
好吧，我会考虑的。
All right, I'll think about it.
-你能相信吗?——我知道。
- Can you believe it? - I know.
-嗨。-我们去吃点东西吧。
- Hey. - Let's go get a snack.
好吧。
Okay.
你在外面挺不错的。
You were, pretty okay out there.
谢谢,维克。
Thanks, Vic.
你应该把这些拿回来。
You should have these back.
我没有烧它们。我刚把它们放进口袋了。
I didn't burn them. I just pocketed them.
我知道，不酷。
I know, not cool.
明年我就不会这么混蛋了，好吗?
I won't be such a jerk next year, all right?
但我将与你为金魔杖而战，夺回我魔法营的霸主地位。
But I will battle you for the Golden Wand and regain my magic camp supremacy.
那就等到明年夏天吧。
Till next summer then.
西奥。
Theo.
嘿。
Hey.
我现在得走了。
I have to go now.
那太糟了。
That's too bad.
-你会打电话给我吗?-我一到家
- You gonna call me? - The second I get home.
这样你就不会忘记。
Just so you don't forget.
哇!
Whoa!
她去了，只是…过于激进。
She went for it, just... Too aggressive.
你鼓励我鼓励她参与…
You did encourage me to encourage her to participate...
这就是你们。
so this is you guys.
有一个声音在你的脑海里。
There's a voice in your head.
那个声音在喊着:“把你的房间打扫干净!”
And that voice is crying out, "Clean up your room!"
不,对不起。那是你爸爸的声音。
Nope, sorry. That was the voice of your dad.
你脑子里的声音在说:“我想成为一个魔术师。”
The voice in your head is saying, "I want to be a magician."
四年前，罗伊·普雷斯顿，
Scribbity-four-ish years ago this guy, Roy Preston,
创立了学院和世界著名的罗伊·普雷斯顿纪念剧院。
founded the institute and the world-famous Roy Preston Prememorial Theater.
现在是罗伊·普雷斯顿纪念剧院
Which is sadly now the Roy Preston Memorial Theater.
在开玩笑。我还在这里。
Kidding. I'm still here.
我请安迪来帮我。
I brought in Andy to help me out.
你将与其他年轻的魔术师建立持久的关系。
You'll build lasting relationships with other young magicians.
即使是那些奇怪的。
Even the weird ones.
因为在这里，我们都是怪胎。
'Cause here, we're all the weird ones.
-真酷，露丝。——谢谢你,安迪。
- Cool bird, Ruth. - Thanks, Andy.
午餐也有不含乳制品的选择。
And the lunch service has nondairy options.
但不要相信我的话。
But don't take my word for it.
问问我们以前的露营者
Just ask any of our former campers,
他们中的许多人现在都是当今最成功的魔术师。
many of whom are now some of the most successful magicians working today.
像我一样，克里斯汀娜·达伍德。
Like me, Kristina Darkwood.
或者你可以亲自到……
Or better yet, come see for yourself at...
神奇的营地!
Magic camp!
是魔法学院。
It's the Institute of Magic.
魔法学院!
The Institute of Magic!